Talk to our team!

Fill out the form below to schedule a demo or call our sales team at  
469-564-3922

Book your demo!

Thank you! Your submission has been received!

Oops! Something went wrong while submitting the form.

By providing your contact information you agree to receive communications from Subsplash including but not limited to emails, phone calls, and text messages. Message and data rates may apply. Message frequency varies. Opt out available. You can learn more about how we handle your personal data and your rights by reviewing our [privacy policy.](https://www.subsplash.com/legal/privacy)

[Join our conversation with Carey Nieuwhof on Oct 9 | Register now!

Register now!](https://equip.subsplash.com/how-thriving-churches-deepen-engagement?utm_campaign=&utm_source=_website_&utm_medium=banner)

* products
    
    
    
    ALL IN ONE
    
    [
    
    Subsplash One
    
    The all-in-one platform to know, grow, and engage your church](https://www.subsplash.com/product/one)
    
    CREATE
    
    [
    
    Apps
    
    Custom-branded mobile and TV apps on all leading devices](https://www.subsplash.com/product/custom-church-apps)[
    
    Websites
    
    Drag-and-drop website builder with advanced SEO tools](https://www.subsplash.com/product/church-websites)
    
    GROW
    
    [
    
    Giving
    
    Mobile, web, and text giving with donor management and analytics](https://www.subsplash.com/product/online-giving)
    
    REACH
    
    [
    
    Media
    
    Media hosting and sermon player with no ads or distractions](https://www.subsplash.com/product/church-media)[
    
    Live streaming
    
    Full HD live streaming to your app, website, and social media](https://www.subsplash.com/product/church-live-streaming)
    
    CONNECT
    
    [
    
    Church management
    
    Child check-in, email builder, volunteers, and service planning](https://www.subsplash.com/product/church-management-software)[
    
    Groups & Messaging
    
    Secure messaging and group engagement for your church](https://www.subsplash.com/product/messaging-for-churches)[
    
    Events
    
    Manage event registrations and payments from one dashboard](https://www.subsplash.com/product/church-event-management)
    
    WHAT’S NEW
    
    [New! Check-in on the Subsplash Platform
    
    Our powerful new software for a simple & seamless check-in process](https://www.subsplash.com/product/check-in-software)[Top 10 challenges facing pastors today
    
    Understanding & navigating the complexities of modern-day ministry](https://www.subsplash.com/blog/pastor-problems)[5 best church donation tracking tools
    
    Explore the top online giving solutions for churches](https://www.subsplash.com/blog/church-donation-tracking-software)[Discipleship training 101: A comprehensive guide
    
    Insights & strategies for effective discipleship training](https://www.subsplash.com/blog/discipleship-training)
    
    TALK TO SALES
    
    [469-564-3922
    
    Connect with a ministry consultant](tel:+1(469)5643922)
    
    [206.965.8090
    
    Connect with a ministry consultant](tel:2069658090)
    
* use cases
    
    
    
    Churches
    
    [
    
    Church plants
    
    First 3 years](https://www.subsplash.com/use-cases/church-plants)[
    
    Neighborhood church
    
    Churches up to 250
    
    Up to 250 people](https://www.subsplash.com/use-cases/neighborhood-church)[
    
    Local church
    
    Churches up to 500
    
    Up to 500 people](https://www.subsplash.com/use-cases/local-church)
    
    [
    
    Regional church
    
    Churches up to 2,000
    
    Up to 2,000 people](https://www.subsplash.com/use-cases/regional-church)[
    
    Mega & multisite
    
    Churches 2,000+
    
    2,000+ people](https://www.subsplash.com/use-cases/mega-church)
    
    More
    
    [
    
    Ministries & nonprofits
    
    Mission-based organizations](https://www.subsplash.com/use-cases/ministries-nonprofits)[
    
    Enterprise solutions
    
    Powerful integrations, API access, and more](https://www.subsplash.com/use-cases/enterprise)
    
    ALL IN ONE
    
    [
    
    Subsplash One
    
    The all-in-one platform to know, grow, and engage your church](https://www.subsplash.com/product/one)
    
    TALK TO SALES
    
    [469-564-3922
    
    Connect with a ministry consultant](tel:+1(469)564-3922)
    
    [206.965.8090
    
    Connect with a ministry consultant](tel:+1(469)564-3922)
    
* RESOURCES
    
    
    
    LEARN
    
    [
    
    Blog
    
    Latest updates for your ministry](https://www.subsplash.com/blog)[
    
    Webinars & events
    
    Industry trends, product announcements, and more](https://www.subsplash.com/resources/webinars)
    
    ENGAGE
    
    [
    
    Free media
    
    Customizable media kits and curated image library](https://www.subsplash.com/free-media-page)[
    
    Ebooks & more
    
    In-depth guides and industry reports](https://www.subsplash.com/resources/ebooks)
    
    [
    
    Equip & Engage
    
    The Subsplash podcast](https://www.subsplash.com/resources/podcast)[
    
    Discipleship content
    
    Special access to world-class resources from leading ministries](https://www.subsplash.com/resources/discipleship-resources)
    
    GET HELP
    
    [Client support
    
    Technical questions and admin support](https://support.subsplash.com/)
    
    [Donor & app user support
    
    Donor account access and other issues](https://support.subsplash.com/en/collections/8595329-end-user-donor-resources)
    
    TALK TO SALES
    
    [469-564-3922
    
    Connect with a ministry consultant](tel:+1(469)564-3922)
    
    [206.965.8090
    
    Connect with a ministry consultant](tel:2069658090)

Privacy Policy
==============

English

español / SPANISH

français / FRENCH

Last updated June 17, 2024 – Version 4.8

This privacy policy describes the collection, use, protection, disclosure, correction, and deletion of your personal information by Subsplash.  Please take a moment to read the following to learn more about our information practices, including what type of information is gathered, how the information is used and for what purposes, to whom we disclose the information, and how we safeguard your personal information.  Your privacy is a priority at Subsplash, and we go to great lengths to protect it.

This privacy policy applies to the websites located at subsplash.com and thechurchapp.com, including all subpages and successor pages, as well as all software and services that we offer, including but not limited to those services that we offer through our websites when you register for a Subsplash account (collectively referred to as the “Subsplash Account Services”).

Subsplash may update its privacy policy from time to time.  When we change the policy in a material way a notice will be posted on our website along with the updated privacy policy.

### WHY WE COLLECT PERSONAL INFORMATION

We collect your personal information because:

* It helps Subsplash deliver and administrate your Subsplash Account Services;
* It helps Subsplash deliver a superior level of customer service;
* It enables Subsplash to give you convenient access to our products and services and focus on categories of greatest interest to you;
* It helps Subsplash keep you posted on the latest product announcements, software updates, special offers, and events that you might like to hear about. If you do not want Subsplash to keep you up to date with Subsplash news, software updates and the latest information on products and services please submit your request [here](https://www.subsplash.com/legal/data-request) or send an email request to [\[email protected\]](https://www.subsplash.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

### WHAT INFORMATION WE COLLECT, WHEN WE COLLECT IT, AND HOW WE MAY USE IT

If you wish to utilize Subsplash Account Services, Subsplash needs your information for purposes of processing and transmitting information to drive the correct data and content between servers and apps for your experience.

Also, there are a number of situations in which your personal information may help us give you better service.  For example:

* We may ask for your personal information when you’re discussing a service issue on the phone with an associate, downloading a software update, registering for a seminar, participating in an online survey, registering your products, or purchasing a product;
* When you interact with Subsplash, we may collect personal information relevant to the situation, such as your name, mailing address, phone number, email address, and contact preferences; your credit card information and information about the Subsplash products you own, such as their serial numbers and date of purchase; and information relating to a support or service issue;
* We collect information regarding customer activities on our websites and applications.  This helps us to determine how best to provide useful information to customers and to understand which parts of our websites, products, and Internet services are of most interest to them, and diagnose problems with our servers and websites;
* When you visit the Subsplash mobile application, we may ask you to opt in to allow us to use GPS technology (or other similar technology) to determine your current location for purposes of reporting on user activity and engagement.  If you do not want us to use your location for the purposes set forth above, you should not opt in or turn off the location services for the Subsplash mobile application located in your account settings or in your mobile phone settings and/or within the mobile application;
* We may use personal information to provide products and/or services that you have requested as well as for auditing, research, and analysis to improve Subsplash’s products; and
* If you utilize the Subsplash messaging functionality, Subsplash stores the contents of your messages which may contain personal information, may obtain your mobile device’s number or your email, and may request access to your mobile device’s contacts for the purpose of accessing and storing only the phone number and/or the email address of the particular persons that you opt to contact through the Service—Subsplash will not copy any contact information regarding persons that you do not contact through the Service.  With regard to the contact information of the particular persons that you opt to contact through the Service, Subsplash will only utilize that information for purposes of providing the Service, and will not use that information for any other purpose;
* If you sign up for Subsplash Messaging, as described above, and you choose to invite other users to join a conversation, Subsplash will request access to your contacts, though it is not required in order to invite other users to your conversation. Subsplash will only use this access to enable you to invite other users.
* Subsplash may use aggregated and anonymized forms of personal information for a variety of purposes, including, but not limited to, analyzing usage trends, fraud detection, and development of new Services.

### PUBLICLY DISPLAYED INFORMATION IS PUBLIC

If you use a bulletin board, streaming service, messaging service, or chat room on a Subsplash website or Service you should be aware that any information you share is visible to other users.  Personally identifiable information you submit to one of these forums can be read, collected, or used by other individuals to send you unsolicited messages.  Subsplash is not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums. For example, if you choose to make information, which was previously non-public, available by disclosing it in such forms or by enabling certain user features, Subsplash will collect that information from your interaction and the information will become publicly available.

### WHEN WE DISCLOSE YOUR INFORMATION

Subsplash takes your privacy very seriously.  Subsplash does not sell or rent your contact information to other marketers or any other third party.  If you wish to utilize the Subsplash Account Services, Subsplash discloses your information to third-party service providers and institutions for purposes of processing and transmitting information to drive the correct data and content between servers and apps for your experience. If you invite other users to one of our services, we may inform the person(s) you invite of who has invited them. Subsplash may share aggregated and anonymized forms of personal information with third parties, in which case, the information shared will be shared in a deidentified and non-identifiable form.

### WITHIN THE SUBSPLASH GROUP

Subsplash, Inc. and Subsplash Wallet, LLC both operate under the name “Subsplash” and they operate as a group.  To help us provide superior service, your personal information may be shared with legal entities within the Subsplash group globally who will take reasonable steps to safeguard it in accordance with Subsplash’s privacy policy.

### WITH OUR SERVICE PROVIDERS, VENDORS, AND STRATEGIC PARTNERS

There are also times when it may be advantageous for Subsplash to make certain personal information about you available to companies that Subsplash has a strategic relationship with or that perform work for Subsplash to provide products and services to you on our behalf.  These companies may help us process information, extend credit, fulfill customer orders, deliver products to you, manage and enhance customer data, provide customer service, assess your interest in our products and services, or conduct customer research or satisfaction surveys.  These companies are also obligated to protect your personal information in strict accordance with Subsplash’s policies, except if we inform you otherwise at the time of collection. Without such information being made available, it would be difficult for you to purchase products, have products delivered to you, receive customer service, provide us feedback to improve our products and services, or access certain services, offers, and content on the Subsplash website.

### PARTNER PROMOTIONS

We may offer contests, sweepstakes, or other promotions with third party partners. If you decide to enter a contest, sweepstakes, or promotion that is sponsored by and/or associated with a third party partner, then the information that you provide will be shared with us and with them. Their use of your information is not governed by this privacy policy.

‍

### BUSINESS TRANSFERS

We may choose to buy or sell assets and may share and/or transfer customer information, including Personal Information, in connection with the evaluation of and entry into such transactions and based on our legitimate interests. Also, if we or our assets are acquired, or if we go out of business, enter bankruptcy, or go through some other change of control, Personal Information may be one of the assets transferred to or acquired by a third party.

### ‍

### LAWFUL REQUESTS

At times we may be required by law or litigation to disclose your personal information.  We may also disclose information about you if we reasonably determine that for national security, law enforcement, or other issues of public importance, disclosure is necessary.

### SUBSPLASH GIVING

Subsplash Giving is web-enabled functionality that can be used with a web browser and on mobile devices.  It was developed by Subsplash to enable donors to donate money to third-party organizations. If you choose to use the Subsplash Giving functionality to donate money, Subsplash and the payment processor will collect personal information from you, including your name, contact information, the donation amounts, and the payment processor receives certain payment information (e.g. credit card number, billing address, security code) and will use that information to process payments and provide you records of the transactions. Donor information will be shared with the Gift Recipient.

When you send a text message to Subsplash or Subsplash Wallet for purposes of utilizing text-to-give functionality, you will be disclosing your cell phone number to Subsplash, Inc., and you thereby consent to receiving a hyperlink to the Subsplash Wallet donation portal via text message. In order to stop receiving texts from Subsplash or Subsplash Wallet, respond to the text message by typing, “STOP.”

### SUBSPLASH LIVE

Subsplash Live utilizes Google (YouTube) API Services, in accordance with the guidelines specified in the [Google Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy) and the [Google API Services User Data Policy](https://developers.google.com/terms/api-services-user-data-policy#additional_requirements_for_specific_api_scopes). Our apps use and transfer of information received from Google APIs to any other app will adhere to the Google API Services User Data Policy, including the Limited Use Requirements.

This access is crucial for obtaining your organization's YouTube channel name and ID, as well as for initiating live streams and broadcasts on behalf of your organization. The objective is to display the connected channel in your Subsplash Dashboard and to create syndicated live broadcasts within that channel. If you decide to revoke Subsplash Live's access to your YouTube data, you can manage this through the Google security settings page at [https://security.google.com/settings/security/permissions](https://security.google.com/settings/security/permissions). For any questions or concerns regarding Subsplash Live's privacy practices, please contact Subsplash.

### COOKIES AND OTHER TECHNOLOGIES

As is standard practice on many corporate websites, Subsplash’s websites use “cookies” and other technologies to help us understand which parts of our websites are the most popular, where our visitors are going, and how much time they spend there.  We also use cookies and other technologies to make sure that our online advertising is bringing customers to our products and services. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer’s hard drive. These cookies are used to store information, such as the time that the current visit occurred, whether the visitor has been to the site before and what site referred the visitor to the web page.

If, however, you prefer not to enable cookies, you can disable them in your browser.  Please note that certain features of the Subsplash websites and Subsplash online products will not be available once cookies are disabled.  As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.  We may also track usage data, such as how frequently you visit our site or use our applications, how many messages you send, and how you engage with our content.

We also use Google Analytics. Google Analytics is a web analytics tool that helps website owners understand how visitors engage with their website.  

Like many services, Google Analytics uses first-party cookies to track visitor interactions as in our case, where they are used to collect information about how visitors use our site. We then use the information to compile reports and to help us improve our site.

We also may use other Google Analytics tools, such as Demographics and Interest Reporting, which enable us to learn more about the characteristics and interests of the users who visit our Site, and Remarketing with Google Analytics, which enables us to provide relevant advertising on different websites and online services.

Google Analytics collects information anonymously.  It reports website trends without identifying individual visitors.  You can opt out of Google Analytics without affecting how you visit our site – for more information on opting out of being tracked by Google Analytics across websites you use, visit this [Google page](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

We use this information, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole.

In some of our email messages we use a “click-through URL” linked to content on the Subsplash website.  When customers click one of these URLs, they pass through our web server before arriving at the destination web page.  We track this click-through data to help us determine interest in particular topics and measure the effectiveness of our customer communications.  If you prefer not to be tracked simply avoid clicking text or graphic links in the email. In addition, we use pixel tags — tiny graphic images — to tell us what parts of our website customers have visited or to measure the effectiveness of searches customers perform on our site.

Pixel tags also enable us to send email messages in a format customers can read.  And they tell us whether emails have been opened to ensure that we’re sending only messages that are of interest to our customers.  We may use this information to reduce or eliminate messages sent to a customer.

### HOW WE PROTECT YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

Subsplash takes precautions — including administrative, technical, and physical measures — to safeguard your personal information against loss, theft, and misuse, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction.  The Subsplash websites use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption on all web pages where personal information is required. To make purchases from the Subsplash online store, or through your Subsplash accounts, you must use an SSL-enabled browser such as Safari, Google, or Internet Explorer.  Doing so protects the confidentiality of your personal and credit card information while it’s transmitted over the Internet. You can help us by also taking precautions to protect your personal data when you are on the Internet. Change your passwords often using a combination of letters and numbers, and make sure you use a secure web browser like Safari or Google.

### INTEGRITY OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

Subsplash allows you to keep your personal information accurate, complete, and up to date.  Naturally, you have the right to access, correct and delete the personal information you have provided, though you may not delete all information if you wish to maintain an account with Subsplash and Subsplash is required to retain some information with regard to Subsplash Giving transactions and donors.  Despite our best efforts, errors sometimes do occur. If you identify any personal information that is out-of-date, incorrect or incomplete, let us know and we will make the corrections promptly and use every reasonable effort to communicate these changes to other parties who may have inadvertently received incorrect or out-of-date personal information from us.  In the event that you delete your information, such deletion may make it impossible for Subsplash to continue offering you some or all of the Subsplash Account Services.

Subsplash retains personal information only as long as we are required to for our business relationship or as required by Federal or Provincial laws, subject to reasonable industry practices for records retention.  Subsplash has appropriate procedures in place with respect to the destruction, deletion and disposition of personal information when it is no longer required by Subsplash, subject to applicable law.

### CHILDREN

Subsplash recognizes that parents, guardians, or other adults often purchase our products for family use, including use by minors.  We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13 for marketing purposes, but because some information is collected electronically, it can appear to be the personal information of the Subsplash purchaser of the product, and will be treated as such by this privacy policy.  If a child under the age of 13 submits personal information to Subsplash without the consent of their parent or guardian and we learn that that personal information is the information of a child under the age of 13, we will delete the information as soon as possible.

We will never share, sell, rent, or transfer children’s personal information other than as described in this section.

We may disclose aggregated information about many of our users which may include aggregated information that does not identify a particular person. In addition, we may disclose children’s personal information:

* To third parties that the child’s parent or guardian approved through the Services.
* If we are required to do so by law or legal process, such as to comply with any court order or subpoena or to respond to any government or regulatory request;
* If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of Subsplash, our customers or others, including to: (1) protect the safety of a child; (2) protect the safety and security of the Services; or (3) enable us to take precautions against liability; or
* To law enforcement agencies or for an investigation related to public safety.

At any time, you may review your child’s personal information maintained by us, require us to correct or delete the personal information, and/or refuse to permit us from further collection or using the child’s information.

You can review, change or delete your child’s personal information by:

* Logging on to your account; or
* Submitting a request [here](https://subsplash.com/legal/data-request), or by sending us an email at [\[email protected\]](https://www.subsplash.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

To protect your privacy and security, we may require you to take certain steps or provide additional information to verify your identity before we provide any information or make corrections.

### CANADA CUSTOMERS

Our policies and practices have been designed to comply with the Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act (Canada), the Privacy Act (Canada) and all provincial statutes that regulate the treatment of personal information in the private and public sectors.

Depending on the location of users of the Subsplash Account Services, information on the Subsplash Account Services including the Subsplash website may be accessed from outside of Canada or sent to others outside of Canada.  Please note that any personal information that is sent outside of Canada may be subject to access by law enforcement and government authorities having jurisdiction in those countries in which the information is located.

If the event that any dispute between you and Subsplash regarding your personal information or this policy is not resolved pursuant to the “Dispute Resolution” section below within thirty (30) days, either party may consult the Privacy Commissioner of Canada or a relevant provincial privacy commissioner.

### PRIVACY NOTICE FOR EU RESIDENTS

This Section \[•\] governs personal data, information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person, gathered from data subjects located in the EU only.  

General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”) Information

The following information describes our commitments to you under EU General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”).

The GDPR makes a distinction between organizations that process personal data for their own purposes (known as "Data Controllers") and organizations that process personal data on behalf of other organizations (known as "Data Processors"). Subsplash only acts as a Data Controller for very limited types of data, such as the information you enter when you register an account with us or the information you submit when purchasing our software.  Subsplash is the Data Controller for information provided by our users when we provide our Services. Subsplash is the Data Processor for information provided by our third party partners when they provide us with services, such as our payment partners processing payments on behalf of our users.

**When We Act as a Data Controller**

When we process your data as a Data Controller, the following applies.  

We collect, use, and share your personal data where we are satisfied that we have an appropriate legal basis to do this. This may be because:  

* Consent:  Our use of your personal data is in accordance with your consent. If we process your personal data based on consent, you will be asked for said consent at or before the time of data collection. You may withdraw your consent at any time, and will not suffer any detriment for withdrawing your consent.
* Contract: Our use of your personal data is to fulfill a contract between you and us.
* Legal Obligation: Our use of your personal data is necessary to comply with a relevant legal or regulatory obligation that we have (for example, where we are required to disclose personal data to a court, or store information due to federal financial regulations); or
* Legitimate Interest: Our use of your personal data is for a legitimate interest of ours, such as fraud prevention and ensuring our network’s security.

Subject to certain exemptions, and in some cases dependent upon the processing activity we are undertaking, EU residents have certain rights in relation to their personal data:  

* Right to Access: You have the right to access your personal data that is being processed; specifically you may request to view your personal data and obtain copies of your personal data.
* Right to Rectification: You have the right to request modifications to your personal data if it is out of date or inaccurate. In some circumstances, you may be able to exercise this right, in whole or in part, through your existing account with us.
* Right of Erasure: You have the right to ask that we delete your personal data.  However, we are not required to comply with your request to erase personal data if the processing of your personal data is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation, or for the establishment, exercise, or defense of legal claims.
* Right to Restriction of Processing: Under certain circumstances, you have the right to request we restrict processing your personal data You have the right to restrict the use of your personal data.  However, we can continue to use your personal data following a request for restriction (a) where we have your consent; (b) to establish, exercise or defend legal claims; or (c) to protect the rights of another natural or legal person.
* Right to Data Portability: To the extent that we process your information (i) based on your consent or under a contract; and (ii) through automated means, you have the right to receive such personal data in a structured, commonly used, machine-readable format, or you can ask to have it transferred directly to another data controller.
* Right to Object: You have the right to object to the processing of your personal data. However, we may still process your personal data if we demonstrate compelling legitimate grounds for the processing which override the interests, rights and freedoms of the data subject or for the establishment, exercise or defense of legal claims.
* Right to Object to Automated Processing:  You have the right to object to decisions based on automated processing, such as where a computer assesses factors in the data we collect about you and makes a determination. We do not currently make any decisions based on automated processing.  

We retain your personal data for as long as necessary to provide you with our services, or for other important purposes such as complying with legal obligations, resolving disputes, and enforcing our agreements.

We ask that you please attempt to resolve any issues regarding your data protection or requests with us first before contacting the relevant supervisory authority.  If you would like to exercise any of the rights described above, please send a request to [\[email protected\]](https://www.subsplash.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). In your message, please indicate the right you would like to exercise and the information that you would like to access, review, correct, or delete.

We may ask you for additional information to confirm your identity and for security purposes, before disclosing the requested personal data.

We may not always be able to fully address your request, for example if it would impact the duty of confidentiality we owe to others, or if we are legally entitled to deal with the request in a different way.

**When Subsplash Acts as a Data Processor**

Where we process your data in our capacity as a Data Processor, the processing of your data will not be governed by the foregoing provisions (“When We Act As Data Controller”), but you can contact the Data Controller directly to learn about their processing of your information and to exercise your rights, or we will forward your request directly to them at your request.

Subsplash’s “privacy by design” approach requires that our default user data protection levels be at the highest setting by default. In the unlikely event of breach, Subsplash will notify data subjects and Supervisory Authorities (SAs) in the EU according to procedures provided in GDPR Articles 33 and 34.  

### EU-US, UK EXTENSION TO THE EU-US, SWISS-US DATA PRIVACY FRAMEWORK

Subsplash, Inc. and its subsidiaries comply with the EU-US Data Privacy Framework (EU-US DPF) and the UK Extension to the EU-US DPF, and the Swiss-US Data Privacy Framework (Swiss-US DPF) set forth by the US Department of Commerce. Subsplash as certified to the US Department of Commerce that it adheres to the EU-US Data Privacy Framework Principles (EU-US DPF Principles) with regard to the process of personal information received from the European Union and the United Kingdom in reliance on the EU-US DPF and the UK Extension to the EU-US DPF. Subsplash has certified to the US Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Swiss-US Data Privacy Framework Principles (Swiss-US DPF Principles) with regard to the processing of personal information received from Switzerland in reliance on the Swiss-US DPF. If there is any conflict between the terms in the privacy policy and the EU-US DPF Principles and/or the Swiss-US DPF Principles, the Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Data Privacy Framework (DPF) Program, and to view our certification, please visit [https://www.dataprivacyframework.gov/](https://www.dataprivacyframework.gov/). Individuals from whom Subsplash collects personal information under the Data Privacy Framework have the right to access their personal data by contacting Subsplash [here](https://www.subsplash.com/legal/data-request) or at [\[email protected\]](https://www.subsplash.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

Subsplash’s compliance with the DPF Principles is subject to the regulatory and enforcement powers of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission.

**Notice and Choice**

When Subsplash collects personal information from individuals, it may share this information with its client organizations or third parties as described above in the Privacy Policy. Individuals should review the privacy policy of the client organization. Individuals will have the choice of signing up for Subsplash services or not.  A link to the Subsplash privacy policy will be provided when individuals are first asked to provide personal information when opting in to Subsplash services.

In instances in which Subsplash is not the controller or collector of the personal information, but only a processor, it has no means of providing individuals with the choice and means for limiting the use and disclosure of their personal information or providing notices when individuals are first asked to provide personal information to Subsplash. In such instances, Subsplash will comply with the instructions of the controller of such information; provide appropriate technical and organizational measures to protect personal data against accidental or unlawful destruction or accidental loss, alteration, unauthorized disclosure or access, and to the extent appropriate, assist the controller in responding to individuals exercising their rights under the Principles.

In the context of an onward transfer Subsplash has responsibility for the processing of personal information it receives under the EU-US and the UK Extension to the EU-US, and Swiss-US Data Privacy Framework and subsequently transfers to a third party acting as an agent on its behalf. Subsplash shall remain liable under the Principles if its agent processes such personal information in a manner inconsistent with the Principles, unless the organization proves that it is not responsible for the event giving rise to the damage.

**Disclosures to Third Parties**

Subsplash will not make disclosures of personal information to third parties without notifying individuals that such disclosure may be made.  In those instances in which Subsplash collects personal information from individuals, prior to disclosing personal information to a third party, Subsplash shall notify the individual of the fact that their information may be disclosed. If individuals do not wish to have their personal information disclosed to any third parties, the individual should not register for such Subsplash services.  With regard to Subsplash Giving, donor information will be shared with the Gift Recipient. The Gift Recipient may utilize a third party for purposes of receipt and management of such information and donors should review the privacy policies of Gift Recipient in this regard. In the case of third parties (e.g., churches) for whom Subsplash gathers personal information, Subsplash shall enter into a contract that provides that such data may only be processed for limited and specified purposes consistent with consent provided and that such third party will provide the same level of protection as is required by the Principles.  For third party agent recipients (e.g., payment processors) of personal information, Subsplash shall: transfer only such data for limited and specified purposes; ascertain that the agent is obligated to provide at least the same level of privacy protection as is required by the Principles, and; upon notice, take reasonable and appropriate steps to stop and remediate unauthorized processing.

**Data Security**

Subsplash shall take reasonable steps to protect personal information from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction. Subsplash has put in place appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration or destruction. Subsplash cannot guarantee the security of information on or transmitted via the Internet.

**Data Integrity**

Subsplash shall only process personal information in a way that is compatible with and relevant for the purpose for which it was collected or authorized by those who provided the information. To the extent necessary for those purposes, Subsplash shall take reasonable steps to ensure that personal information is accurate, complete, current and reliable for its intended use.

**Access**

In those instances in which Subsplash collects personal information directly from individuals, Subsplash shall allow those individuals access to their personal information and allow the individual to correct, amend or delete inaccurate information, except where the burden or expense of providing access would be disproportionate to the risks to the privacy of the individual in the case in question or where the rights of persons other than the individual would be violated.  As noted above, you may not delete all information if you wish to maintain an account with Subsplash and Subsplash is required to retain some information with regard to Subsplash Giving transactions and the applicable users.

**Recourse, Enforcement, and Liability**

A)  Dispute Resolution

If you filed a complaint with Subsplash and it has not been properly addressed, JAMS is designated by Subsplash as the independent dispute resolution body to address complaints regarding Subsplash’s collection of personal information and provide appropriate recourse.  Such body will not charge the complaining party for its services. Follow this [link](https://www.jamsadr.com/file-an-eu-us-privacy-shield-or-safe-harbor-claim) to the complaint submission form for the above referenced independent dispute resolution body.

B)  Binding Arbitration

If your claims as to data covered by the EU-US and the UK Extension to the EU-US, and Swiss-US Data Privacy Framework have not been remedied through dispute resolution directly with Subsplash or through independent dispute resolution as described above, such “residual claims” may be heard by a “Data Privacy Framework Panel” composed of one or three arbitrators as agreed upon by the parties.  The Panel may only award individual-specific, non-monetary equitable relief (e.g. access, correction, deletion of the individual’s data in question) necessary to remedy the violation of the Principles only with respect to the individual.  Damages, costs, fees and other remedies may not be awarded, and each party bears its own attorney’s fees.  This arbitration option is only available for an individual to determine for such “residual claims” whether Subsplash has violated its obligations under the Principles as to that individual and whether any such violation remains fully or partially unremedied.

C)  GDPR (General Data Protection Regulation)

The GDPR replaces Directive 95/46/EC and becomes enforceable on May 25, 2018. The following statement is intended to supplement the preceding discussion of the EU-U.S. Data Privacy Framework. As to personal data collected and controlled by Subsplash, subject to the qualifications and limitations stated in the preceding discussion, EU data subjects retain their full rights to be informed of the purposes of our processing activities at collection; to withdraw consent; to access, rectify, transport, and erase their personal data; to object to processing for direct marketing efforts; and to object when subjected to automated processing decisions. As to personal data collected by third parties, and as to which Subsplash is a mere processor, EU data subjects should contact the controller (e.g., church or ministry) with regard to their rights to be informed of the purposes of our processing activities at collection; to withdraw consent; to access, rectify, transport, and erase their personal data; to object to processing for direct marketing efforts; and to object when subjected to automated processing decisions.  Such rights may be subject to certain qualifications and limitations as stated in the discussion of EU-US and the UK Extension to the EU-US, and Swiss-US Data Privacy Framework.

Our Data Protection Officers will assist EU residents with these requests free of charge and may be contacted at [\[email protected\]](https://www.subsplash.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

Subsplash understands that the adoption of global data security practices is not a one-time activity.  Subsplash’s “privacy by design” approach requires that our default user data protection levels be at the highest setting by default. In the unlikely event of breach, Subsplash will notify data subjects and Supervisory Authorities (SAs) in the EU according to procedures provided in GDPR Articles 33 and 34.

We do not intentionally collect personal data from, and do not tailor any services to, children.

VeraSafe has been appointed as Subsplash's representative in the European Union for data protection matters, pursuant to Article 27 of the General Data Protection Regulation of the European Union. VeraSafe can be contacted in addition to the Privacy Officer, only on matters related to the processing of personal data. To make such an inquiry, please contact VeraSafe using this [contact form](https://www.verasafe.com/privacy-services/contact-article-27-representative) or via telephone at: +420 228 881 031.

Alternatively, VeraSafe can be contacted at:

VeraSafe Ireland Ltd.

Unit 3D North Point House

North Point Business Park

New Mallow Road

Cork T23AT2P

Ireland

### DATA PRIVACY FOR CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS

This section applies solely to visitors and users of our Site and Services who reside in the State of California. We have adopted this notice to comply with the California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018 (the “CCPA”) and the California Online Privacy Protection Act (“CalOPPA”), and any terms defined in the CCPA or CalOPPA have the same meaning when used in this notice.

For the purposes of this section “California Data Subject” shall mean: (1) an individual who is in the State of California for other than a temporary or transitory purpose, and (2) an individual who is domiciled in the State of California who is outside the State of California for a temporary or transitory purpose.

**Information We Collect**

Subsplash collects information that identifies, relates to, describes, references, is capable of being associated with, or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, with a particular California Data Subject or device ("personal information"). In particular, Subsplash has collected the following categories of personal information from California Data Subjects within the last twelve (12) months:

CATEGORY

Example

DO WE COLLECT THIS DATA?

Indentifiers

Real name, alias, postal address, unique personal identifier, online identifier, internet protocol (IP) address, email address, account name, social security number, driver’s license number, passport number, or other similar identifiers

Yes

Characteristics of protected classifications under California or federal law

Race, gender, ethnicity, disability status

No

Commercial information

Records of personal property, products, or services purchased, obtained, or considered, or other purchasing or consuming histories or tendencies

Yes

Biometric information

Fingerprint, facial pattern, voice, typing cadence

Yes

Internet or other electronic network activity information

Information regarding usage of a site, software, or app

Yes

Geolocation data

Physical location

Yes

Audio, electronic, visual, thermal, olfactory, or similar information

Recordings of a California Data Subject

Yes

Professional or employment-related information

Place of work, current occupation, duration of occupation, position/title

Yes

Education Information

Information that is not publicly available personally identifiable information as defined in the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA)

No

Inferences drawn from any of the information identified above

Information used to create a profile about the California Data Subject reflecting their preferences, characteristics, psychological trends, predispositions, behavior, attitudes, intelligence, abilities, and aptitudes

Yes

Sources of Personal Information. Subsplash obtains the personal information listed above from the following sources:

Source

Example

Do we receive from this source?

Directly from you

From forms you complete or orders for products and services you purchase.

Yes

Indirectly from you

From observing your actions on the Service

Yes

Third Parties

We are provided information by our third party vendors such as:

* Authentication Partners (who may provide us with personal information regarding users who authenticate with our Services through a third party)
* Technology Service Providers (who may provide us personal information in the form of usage information, IP addresses, etc. of users of our Site and Services)
* Payment Partners (who may provide us personal information in order to process payments from users)
* Advertising Partners (Who may provide information about users viewing our advertisements)

Yes

**Use of Personal Information**

We may use or disclose the personal information we collect for one or more of the following business purposes:

A) To fulfill the purpose for which you provided the information. For example, if you share your name and contact information to request a price quote or ask a question about our products or services, we will use that personal information to respond to your inquiry. If you create an account on our Services the personal information you provide as part of the account creation process may be visible to other account holders, and we may use that information to verify your identity when you access the account. We may use personal information you provide us to provide technical support.  In addition, we may use the above information:

a)  To provide, support, personalize, and develop our websites, products, and/or services;

b)  To create, maintain, customize, and secure your account with us;

c)  To process your requests, purchases, transactions, and payments and prevent transactional fraud;

d)  To provide you with support and to respond to your inquiries, including to investigate and address your concerns and monitor and improve our responses;

e)  To help maintain the safety, security, and integrity of our Website, products and services, databases and other technology assets, and business;

f)  To respond to law enforcement requests and as required by applicable law, court order, or governmental regulations; and

g)  As described to you when collecting your personal information or as otherwise set forth in the CCPA.

Subsplash will not collect additional categories of personal information or use the personal information we collected for materially different, unrelated, or incompatible purposes without providing you notice.  

Subsplash does not sell your personal information.  Subsplash does share personal information with our third party service providers and vendors in order to provide you the Service.

**Your Rights and Choices**

This section describes your CCPA rights and explains how to exercise those rights.

You have the right to request that we disclose certain information to you about our collection and use of your personal information over the past 12 months. Once we receive and verify your request, we will disclose to you:

A)  The categories of personal information we collected about you;

B)  The categories of sources for the personal information we collected about you;

C)  Our business or commercial purpose for collecting or selling that personal information;

D)  The categories of third parties with whom we share that personal information;

E)  The specific pieces of personal information we collected about you (also called a data portability request);

F)  If we sold or disclosed your personal information for a business purpose, two separate lists disclosing:

a)  sales, identifying the personal information categories that each category of recipient purchased; and

b)  disclosures for a business purpose, identifying the personal information categories that each category of recipient obtained.

You have the right to request that we delete any of your personal information that we collected from you and retained, subject to certain exceptions. Once we receive and verify your request, we will delete (and direct our service providers to delete) your personal information from our records, unless an exception applies.

We may deny your deletion request if retaining the information is necessary for us or our service providers to:

A)  Complete the transaction for which we collected the personal information, provide a good or service that you requested, take actions reasonably anticipated within the context of our ongoing business relationship with you, or otherwise perform our contract with you;

B)  Detect security incidents, protect against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent, or illegal activity, or prosecute those responsible for such activities;

C)  Debug products to identify and repair errors that impair existing intended functionality;

D)  Exercise free speech, ensure the right of another California Data Subject to exercise their free speech rights, or exercise another right provided for by law;

E)  Comply with the California Electronic Communications Privacy Act (Cal. Penal Code § 1546 seq.);

F)  Engage in public or peer-reviewed scientific, historical, or statistical research in the public interest that adheres to all other applicable ethics and privacy laws, when the information's deletion may likely render impossible or seriously impair the research's achievement, if you previously provided informed consent;

G)  Enable solely internal uses that are reasonably aligned with California Data Subject expectations based on your relationship with us;

H)  Comply with a legal obligation; and

I)  Make other internal and lawful uses of that information that are compatible with the context in which you provided it.

To exercise the access, data portability, and deletion rights described above, please submit a verifiable California Data Subject request to us by submitting a request [here](https://www.subsplash.com/legal/data-request) or by sending us an email at [\[email protected\]](https://www.subsplash.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) or calling us at (206) 965-8090.

Only you or a person registered with the California Secretary of State, that you authorize to act on your behalf, may make a verifiable California Data Subject request related to your personal information. You may also make a verifiable California Data Subject request on behalf of your minor child.

You may only make a verifiable California Data Subject request for access or data portability twice within a twelve (12) month period. The verifiable California Data Subject request must:

A)  Provide sufficient information that allows us to reasonably verify you are the person about whom we collected personal information or an authorized representative; and

B)  Describe your request with sufficient detail that allows us to properly understand, evaluate, and respond to it.

We cannot respond to your request or provide you with personal information if we cannot verify your identity or authority to make the request and confirm the personal information relates to you.  Making a verifiable California Data Subject request does not require you to create an account with us.  We will only use personal information provided in a verifiable California Data Subject request to verify the requestor's identity or authority to make the request.

We aspire to respond to a verifiable California Data Subject request within forty five (45) days of receipt of the request.  If we require more time (up to ninety (90) days) we will inform you of the reason(s) why an extension is needed and how long we anticipate the period to be.  Any disclosure we provide will only cover the twelve (12) month period preceding the receipt of your request.  If applicable, the response may provide the reasons why we cannot comply with your request.  For data portability requests, we will select a format to provide your personal information that is readily useable and should allow you to transmit the information from one entity to another entity without hindrance.

We do not charge a fee to process or respond to your verifiable California Data Subject request unless it is excessive, repetitive, or manifestly unfounded.  If we determine that the request warrants a fee, we will tell you why we made that decision and provide you with a cost estimate before completing your request.  We reserve the right to refuse to respond to verifiable California Data Subject requests that are excessive, repetitive, or manifestly unfounded.

**Right of Non-Discrimination**

We will not discriminate against you for exercising any of your CCPA rights. We will not take any of the following actions against you in response to an exercise of your rights:

A)  Deny you goods or services.

B)  Charge you different prices or rates for goods or services, including through granting discounts or other benefits, or imposing penalties.

C)  Provide you a different level or quality of goods or services.

D)  Suggest that you may receive a different price or rate for goods or services or a different level or quality of goods or services.

**California Do-Not-Track Disclosures**

Subsplash does not track its customers over time and across third party websites to provide targeted advertising and therefore does not respond to Do Not Track (DNT) signals.  Third parties that have content embedded on Subsplash’s websites, software, or mobile applications (e.g. social features) may set cookies on a user’s browser and/or obtain information about the fact that a web browser visited a specific Subsplash website from a certain IP address.  Third parties cannot collect any other personal identifiable information from Subsplash’s websites unless you provide it to them directly.

**Special Information for Nevada Residents**

Residents of the State of Nevada have the right to opt out of the sale of certain pieces of their information to other companies who will sell or license their information to others. Subsplash does not sell or rent your contact information to other marketers or any other third party. If you are a Nevada resident and have additional questions please contact us [here](https://www.subsplash.com/legal/data-request) or by email at [\[email protected\]](https://www.subsplash.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

‍

### SPECIALIZED PARTNER CAMPAIGNS

From time-to-time, Subsplash may work with partner organizations to develop and distribute specialized content. Users who participate in the specialized marketing campaigns by completing our lead form and downloading the applicable content will be subject to the [Supplemental Privacy Notice](https://www.subsplash.com/legal/supplemental-privacy-notice) in addition to this Privacy Policy.

‍

### OUR COMPANY-WIDE COMMITMENT TO YOUR PRIVACY

To make sure your personal information is secure, we communicate these privacy guidelines to Subsplash employees and strictly enforce privacy safeguards within the company.

### FREEDOM OF INFORMATION REQUESTS

If you are communicating with or making a donation to any organization or institution that is subject to either federal or provincial public sector “freedom of information” or “access to information” legislation, then please note that information concerning your communication and/or donation may disclosed to third parties pursuant to the procedures available under those laws.

### INQUIRIES, COMPLAINTS, AND DISPUTE RESOLUTION

If you wish to verify, correct or delete any personal information we have collected, or if you have any questions or concerns, or if you have any complaints, please contact us [here](https://www.subsplash.com/legal/data-request) or by email at [\[email protected\]](https://www.subsplash.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). If there is a dispute between you and Subsplash regarding your personal information or this policy, you agree to use reasonable efforts to resolve such dispute with Subsplash informally and to consult and negotiate with Subsplash in good faith to reach a fair and equitable solution.

###   
PRIVACY QUESTIONS

If you have questions or concerns about Subsplash’s privacy policy, please contact our Privacy Officer.  Our Privacy Officer can be contacted at:

Subsplash, Inc.

5473 Blair Rd. Ste 100, PMB 41141, Dallas, TX 75231-4227

Email: [\[email protected\]](https://www.subsplash.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

Última actualización: 27 de Septiembre de 2022 - Versión 4.6 

La presente política de privacidad describe la recopilación, el uso, la protección, la divulgación, la corrección y la eliminación de su información personal por parte de Subsplash. Sírvase tomar un momento para leer lo siguiente y saber más sobre nuestras prácticas de información, incluso el tipo de información que recopilamos, de qué modo usamos la información y con qué objetivo, a quién le divulgamos la información y cómo protegemos su información personal. Su privacidad es una prioridad de Subsplash y hacemos todo lo posible para protegerla. 

La presente política de privacidad corresponde a los sitios web ubicados en subsplash.com y thechurchapp.com incluso las subpáginas y páginas sucesoras, así como todo el software y los servicios que ofrecemos, incluso, pero sin estar limitados a los servicios que ofredemos a traves de nuestros sitios web cuando se inscribe en una cuenta de Subsplash (mencionados colectivamente como los "Servicios de la cuenta de Subsplash. 

Subsplash puede actualizar su política de privacidad de vez en cuando. Cuando cambiemos la política sustancialmente se pondrá una notificación en nuestro sitio web junto con la política de privacidad actualizada.

‍

### POR QUÉ RECOPILAMOS INFORMACIÓN PERSONAL

Recopilamos su información personal porque: 

* Ayuda a Subsplash a entregar y administra sus Servicios de a cuenta de Subsplash
* Ayuda a que Subsplash proporcione un nivel superior de servicio al cliente. 
* Permite que Subsplash le brinde un acceso conveniente a nuestros 'productos y servicios y que se centre en categorías que tengan el mayor interés para usted.
* Ayuda a que Subsplash lo mantenga informado de las más recientes notificaciones de productos, actualizaciones del software, ofertas especiales y acontedimientos sobre los que le interesaría saber. Si no desea que Subsplash lo mantenga actualizado con noticias de Subsplash, actualizaciones de software y la información más reciente sobre productos y servicios, envié su solicitud [aquí](https://www.subsplash.com/legal/data-request) o envíe una solicitud por correo electrónico a [\[email protected\]](https://www.subsplash.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

### QUÉ INFORMACIÓN RECOPILAMOS, CUÁNDO LA RECOPILAMOS Y CÓMO PODEMOS USARLA

Si desea utilizar los Servicios de la cuenta de Subsplash, Subsplash necesita su información con el fin de procesar y transmitir información para transferir los datos y el contenido correcto entre servidores y aplicaciones para su experiencia. 

También, hay una serie de situaciones en las que su información personal puede ayudarnos a brindarle un servicio mejor. Por ejemplo:

* Podemos pedirle información personal cuando hable por teléfono con un asociado sobre un problema de servicio, cuando baje una actualización de software, se registre para un seminario, participe en una encuesta en línea, registre sus productos o compre un producto
* Cuando interactúa con Subsplash, podemos recopilar información personal pertinente a la situación, tal como su nombre, dirección postal, número de teléfono, dirección de correo electrónico y preferencias de contacto; información sobre su tarjeta de crédito e información sobre los productos de Subsplash que posee, tal como sus números de serie y fecha de compra; e información relacionada con un problema de soporte o servicio;
* Recopilamos información sobre las actividades de los clientes en nuestros sitios web y en nuestras aplicaciones. Esto nos ayuda a determinar cual es la mejor manera de proporcionales información útil a los clientes y comprender que parte de nuestros sitios web, productos y servicios de Internet les interesan más y diagnosticar problemas con nuestros servidores y sitios web;
* Cuando visite la aplicación móvil Subsplash, podemos pedirle que opte por permitirnos usar la tecnología GPS (u otra tecnología similar) para determinar su ubicación actual con el propósito de comunicar la actividad y dedicación del usuario. Si no desea que usemos su ubicación con el objetivo establecido anteriormente, no debe optar participar ni desactivar los servicios de ubicación para la aplicación móvil Subsplash ubicada en la configuración de su cuenta o en la configuración de su teléfono móvil y/o dentro de la aplicación móvil;
* Podemos utilizar la información personal para proporcionar productos y/o servicios que haya solicitado, así como para auditoría, investigación y análisis para mejorar los productos de Subsplash;
* Si usted utiliza la funcionalidad de mensajería de Subsplash, Subsplash guarda el contenido de sus mensajes, los que pueden contener información personal, puede obtener el número de su dispositivo móvil o su correo electrónico y puede solicitar acceso a los contactos de su dispositivo móvil con el objetivo de acceder y almacenar solo el número de teléfono y/o la dirección de correo electrónico, en particular de las personas con las que opta contactar a través del Servicio - Subsplash no copiará ningúna información de contacto relacionada con las personas con las que no se comunica a través del Servicio. En lo que se refiere a la información de contacto, en particular de las personas con las que ha optado contactar por medio del Servicio, Subsplash solo utilizará la información con el objetivo de proporcionar el Servicio y no usará la información con ningún otro objetivo. 
* Si se inscribe en Subsplash Messaging, como se describió anteriormente, y decide invitar a otros usuarios a participar en una conversación, Subsplash solicitará acceso a sus contactos, aunque no es un requisito para invitar a otros usuarios a su conversación Subsplash solo usará este acceso para permitirle que invite a otros usuarios;
* Subsplash puede utilizar formas agregadas y anónimas de información personal para una variedad de propósitos, que incluyen, sin estar limitados a ellos, el análisis del uso, la detección de fraudes y el desarrollo de nuevos Servicios

### LA INFORMACIÓN MOSTRADA PÚBLICAMENTE ES PÚBLICA 

Si utiliza un tablón de anuncios, un servicio de transmisión por Internet ("streaming"), un servicio de mensajería o una sala de chat en un sitio web o servicio de Subsplash, debe estas consciente de que cualquier información que comparta la pueden ver otros usuarios. La información personal identificable que envíe a esos foros la pueden leer, recopilar o usar otras personas para enviarle mensajes no solicitados. Subsplash no es responsable de la información personal identificable que decida enviar en estos foros. Por ejemplo, si decide que la información que no era pública anteriormente esté disponible divulgándola en dichos formularios o activando ciertas funciones de usuario, Subsplash recopilará esa información de su interacción y la información estará disponible públicamente. 

### CUANDO DIVULGAMOS SU INFORMACIÓN

Subsplash toma muy en serio su privacidad Subsplash no vende ni alquila su información de contacto a otros comerciantes o a ningún otro tercero. Si desea utilizar los Servicios de la cuenta de Subsplash, Subsplash divulga su información a proveedores de terceros y a instituciones con el fin de procesar y transmitir información para transferir los datos y el contenido correcto entre servidores y aplicaciones para su experiencia. Si invita a otros usuarios a uno de nuestros servicios, podemos informar a la(s) persona(s) que invita(n) quién los ha invitado. Subsplash puede compartir formas agregadas y anónimas de información personal con terceros, en cuyo caso, la información compartida se compartirá de forma desidentificada y no identificable. 

### Dentro del grupo Subsplash

Ambos, Subsplash, Inc. y Subsplash Wallet, LLC, operan bajo el nombre de "Subsplash" y operan como un grupo. Para ayudarnos a proporcionar un servicio de gran calidad, su información personal puede compartirse con entidades legales dentro del grupo Subsplash a nivel mundial, quienes tomarán medidas razonables para protegerla de acuerdo con la política de privacidad de Subsplash. 

### CON NUESTROS PROVEEDORES DE SERVICIOS, VENDEDORES Y SOCIOS ESTRATÉGICOS

Algunas veces también puede ser una ventaja para Subsplash poner cierta información personal sobre usted a la disposición de empresas con las que Subsplash tiene una relación estratégica o que desempeñan trabajo para que Subsplash le proporcione a usted productos y servicios en nuestro nombre. Estas compañías pueden ayudarnos a procesar información, extender crédito, cumplir con los pedidos de los clientes, entregarle productos, administrar y mejorar los datos de los clientes, proporcionar servicio al cliente, evaluar su interés en nuestros productos y servicios, o llevar a cabo análisis de clientes o encuestas de satisfacción. Estas compañías también están obligadas a proteger su información personal estrictamente de acuerdo con las políticas de Subsplash, excepto si le informamos a usted lo contrario en el momento de la recopilación. Sin la disponibilidad de dicha información, sería sería difícil para usted comprar productos, la entrega de productos, recibir servicio al cliente, proporcionarnos comentarios para mejorar nuestros productos y servicios, o acceder ciertos servicios, ofertas, y contenido en el sitio web de Subsplash. 

### PROMOCIONES DE SOCIOS

Podemos ofrecer concursos, sorteos u otras promociones con terceros asociados. Si decide participar en un concurso, un sorteo o una promoción patrocinada o asociada a un tercero asociado, la información que usted proporcione será compartida con nosotros y con ellos. El uso de su información por ellos no se rige por esta política de privacidad.

### TRANSFERENCIAS DE NEGOCIOS

Podemos optar por comprar o vender activos y podemos compartir y/o transferir la información de los clientes incluyendo la Información Personal, en relación con la evaluación y la entrada en tales transacciones y basados en nuestros intereses legítimos. Además, si nosotros o nuestros activos son adquiridos, o si cerramos el negocio, entramos en bancarrota o sufrimos algún otro cambio de control, la información personal puede ser uno de los activos transferidos o adquiridos por un tercero.

### SOLICITUDES LEGALES

A veces, es posible que la ley o los litigios nos exijan divulgar su información personal. También podemos divulgar información sobre usted si determinamos razonablemente que la divulgación es necesaria para la seguridad nacional, el cumplimiento de la ley y otros asuntos de importancia pública. 

### SUBSPLASH GIVING

Subsplash Giving es una funcionalidad habilitada para la web que se puede utilizar con un navegador web y en aparatos móviles. Subsplash la desarrolló para permitir que los donantes hagan sus donaciones monetarias a organizaciones de terceros Si decide utilizar la funcionalidad Subsplash Giving para donar dinero, Subsplash y el procesador de pagos recopilarán información personal de usted, lo que incluye su nombre, información de contacto, la cantidad de las donaciones. El procesador de pagos recibe cierta información de pago (por ejemplo, número de tarjeta de crédito, dirección de facturación, código de seguridad) y utilizará esa información para procesar pagos y proporcionarle registros de las transacciones. La información del donante se compartirá con el Destinatario del Regalo. 

Cuando usted le envía un mensaje a Subsplash o a Subsplash Wallet con el objetivo de utilizar la función de donativos por texto, estará divulgando el número de su celular a Subsplash, Inc. y, por lo tanto, da su consentimiento para recibir un hipervínculo al portal de donativos de Subsplash Wallet por medio de un texto. Para dejar de recibir textos de Subsplash y Subsplash Wallet, responda "STOP" al mensaje de texto.

### SUBSPLASH LIVE

Subsplash Live utiliza los Servicios API de YouTube, regidos por la Política de Privacidad de Google ([http://www.google.com/policies/privacy](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy)), para acceder al nombre del canal de YouTube de su organización y la identificación y para crear transmisiones por Internet y transmisiones televisivas en vivo a nombre de su organización. Hacemos esto para mostrar el canal vinculado en su Subsplash Dashboard y para crear transmisiones en vivo sindicadas en ese canal. Además del procedimiento normal de Subsplash para borrar los datos almacenados, su organización puede revocar el acceso de Subsplash Live a los datos de usted en YouTube por medio de la página de configuración de seguridad de Google ([https://security.google.com/settings/security/permissions](https://security.google.com/settings/security/permissions)). Sírvase ponerse en contacto con Subsplash si tiene alguna pregunta o queja sobre las prácticas de privacidad de Subsplash Live. 

### Cookies y otras tecnologías

Al igual que la práctica estándar de muchos sitios web corporativos, los sitios web de Subsplash utilizan "cookies" y otras tecnologías para ayudarnos a comprender qué partes de nuestros sitios web son las más populares, a dónde se dirigen nuestros visitantes y cuánto tiempo pasan allí. También usamos cookies y otras tecnologías para asegurarnos de que nuestra publicidad en línea atrae a los clientes a nuestros productos y servicios. Las cookies contienen información que se transfiere al disco duro de su ordenador. Estas cookies se usan para almacenar información, como el momento en que se produjo la visita actual, si el visitante ha estado en el sitio antes y qué sitio refirió al visitante a la página web. 

Sin embargo, si prefiere no activar las cookies, puede desactivarlos en su navegador. Fíjese que ciertas características de los sitios web de Subsplash y los productos en línea de Subsplash no estarán disponibles una vez que se desactiven las cookies. As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. Esta información incluye direcciones de Protocolo de Internet (IP), el tipo de navegador, el Proveedor de Servicios de Internet (ISP), páginas que lo han referido a esta/páginas de salida, sistema operativo, marca de fecha/hora y datos de flujo de clics. También podemos realizar un seguimiento de los datos de uso, tal como la frecuencia con la que usted visita nuestro sitio o usa nuestras aplicaciones, cuántos mensajes envía y cómo interactúa con nuestro contenido. 

También usamos Google Analytics. Google Analytics es una herramienta de análisis de la web que ayuda a los propietarios de sitios web a comprender cómo los visitantes interactúan con su sitio web. 

Como en muchos servicios, Google Analytics utiliza cookies propias para seguir las interacciones de los visitantes, como en nuestro caso, donde se utilizan para obtener información sobre cómo los visitantes usan nuestro sitio. Entonces, usamos la información para reunir informes y ayudarnos a mejorar nuestro sitio. 

También podemos utilizar otras herramientas de Google Analytics, tales como Demographics and Interest Reporting (informes sobre datos demográficos y de intereses), que nos permiten saber más sobre las características e intereses de los usuarios que visitan nuestro Sitio y el Remarketing (nueva comercialización) con Google Analytics, que nos permite proporcionar publicidad relevante en diferentes sitios web y servicios en línea. 

Google Analytics recopila información de modo anónimo. It reports website trends without identifying individual visitors. Usted tiene la opción de no participar (opt out) en Google Analytics sin que eso afecte cómo visita nuestro sitio: para obtener más información sobre cómo optar para que Google Analytics no lo siga por todos los sitios web que utiliza, visite esta [página de Google](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout). Usamos esta información para analizar tendencias, para administrar el sitio, para seguir los movimientos de los usuarios por el sitio y para recopilar información demográfica sobre nuestra base de usuarios en total. 

En algunos de nuestros mensajes de correo electrónico usamos un "URL de paso" (click-through URL) vinculado al contenido del sitio web de Subsplash. Cuando los clientes hacen clic en uno de estos URLs, pasan por nuestro servidor web antes de llegar a la página web de su destino. Monitorizamos esos datos de enlace de paso para ayudarnos a determinar el interés en temas en particular y medir la efectividad de nuestras comunicaciones con los clientes. Si prefiere que no lo hagamos, simplemente evite hacer clic en los enlaces de texto o gráficos del mensaje electrónico. Además, utilizamos píxels transparentes (pequeñas imágenes gráficas) para que nos indiquen las partes de nuestro sitio web que han visitado los clientes o para medir la efectividad de las búsquedas que llevan a cabo los clientes en nuestro sitio. 

Los pixeles transparentes también nos permiten enviar mensajes de correo electrónico en un formato que los clientes puedan leer y nos dicen si se han abierto los correos electrónicos para estar seguros de que solo estamos enviando mensajes que son de interés para nuestros clientes. Podemos usar esta información para disminuir o eliminar la cantidad de mensajes que se le envían a los clientes.

### CÓMO PROTEGEMOS SU INFORMACIÓN PERSONAL

Subsplash toma precauciones, entre las que se incluyen medidas administrativas, técnicas y físicas, para proteger su información personal contra pérdida, robo y uso indebido, así como el acceso, divulgación, alteración y destrucción no autorizados. Los sitios web de Subsplash usan la codificación con Capas de Protección Segura (SSL) en todas las páginas web donde se requiere información personal. Para hacer compras en la tienda en línea de Subsplash o a través de sus cuentas de Subsplash, debe usar un navegador habilitado para SSL como Safari, Google o Internet Explorer. Hacerlo protege la confidencialidad de su información personal y la de su tarjeta de crédito mientras se transmiten por Internet. También nos puede ayudar tomando precauciones para proteger sus datos personales cuando está en Internet. Cambie sus contraseñas con frecuencia usando una combinación de letras y números y asegúrese de usar un navegador web seguro como Safari o Google.  

### LA INTEGRIDAD DE SU INFORMACIÓN PERSONAL

Subsplash le permite mantener su información personal correcta, completa y actualizada. Como es natural, usted tiene el derecho a acceder, corregir y borrar la información personal que ha proporcionado, aunque no puede borrar toda la información si desea mantener una cuenta con Subsplash. Se le exige a Subsplash que retenga cierta información en lo que se refiere a las transacciones y donantes de Subsplash Giving. A pesar de nuestros mejores esfuerzos, algunas veces ocurren errores. Si identifica cualquier información personal que no esté actualizada, esté incorrecta o incompleta, háganoslo saber y la rectificaremos sin demora. Haremos todo esfuerzo razonable para dar a conocer estos cambios a otras partes que, sin advertirlo, puedan haber recibido información personal incorrecta o no actualizada de nuestra parte. En el caso de que usted borre su información, haberlo hecho puede hacer imposible que Subsplash continúe ofreciéndole algunos o todos los Servicios de la cuenta de Subsplash. Subsplash retiene información personal solo mientras se exije que lo hagamos para nuestra relación comercial o según lo exijan las leyes federales o provinciales, sujeto a prácticas razonables de la industria para la retención de registros. Subsplash cuenta con procedimientos adecuados en lo que se refiere a destruir, borrar y disponer de información personal cuando Subsplash no la necesite más, sujeta a las leyes correspondientes. 

### MENORES DE EDAD

Subsplash reconoce que los padres, tutores u otros adultos a menudo compran nuestros productos para uso de la familia que incluye el uso por menores. No recopilamos información personal de niños menores de 13 años a sabiendas con fines de marketing, pero debido a que cierta información se recopila electrónicamente, puede parecer que es la información personal del comprador del producto de Subsplash y será tratada como tal por esta política de privacidad. Si un niño menor de 13 años envía información personal a Subsplash sin el consentimiento de sus padres o tutores y nos enteramos de que esa información personal es la información de un niño menor de 13 años, borraremos la información lo antes posible. 

Nunca compartiremos, venderemos, alquilaremos ni transferiremos información personal de menores que no sea como se describe en esta sección. 

Podemos divulgar información agregada sobre muchos de nuestros usuarios la que puede incluir información agregada que no identifica a una persona en particular, además, es posible que divulguemos información personal de los menores:

* A terceros que el padre o tutor del niño aprobó a través de los Servicios. 
* Si estamos obligados a hacerlo por ley o proceso legal, como para cumplir con cualquier orden judicial o citación o para responder a cualquier solicitud gubernamental o regulatoria; 
* Si creemos que la divulgación es necesaria o apropiada para proteger los derechos, la propiedad o la seguridad de Subsplash, de nuestros clientes u otros, incluso para: (1) proteger la seguridad de un menor de edad; (2) proteger la seguridad de los Servicios; o (3) permitirnos tomar precauciones contra la responsabilidad civil; o 
* A las agencias de orden público o para una investigación relacionada con la seguridad pública. 

En cualquier momento, puede revisar la información personal de su hijo guardada por nosotros, exigirnos que corrijamos o borremos la información personal y/o negarse a permitirnos seguir recopilando o usando la información del menor. 

Puede revisar, cambiar o borrar la información personal de su hijo al: 

* Iniciar la sesión en su cuenta; o 
* Enviando una solicitud [aquí](https://subsplash.com/legal/data-request), o enviándonos un correo electrónico a [\[email protected\]](https://www.subsplash.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). Para proteger su privacidad y seguridad, es posible que le solicitemos que tome ciertas medidas o proporcione información adicional para verificar su identidad antes de darle cualquier información o corregirla.

### CLIENTES DEL CANADÁ

Nuestras políticas y prácticas han sido diseñadas para cumplir con las leyes canadienses llamadas "Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act" (Ley de Protección de Información Personal y Documentos Electrónicos), "Privacy Act" (Ley de Privacidad) y todos los estatutos provinciales que regulan el tratamiento de la información personal en los sectores privado y público. 

Según la ubicación de los usuarios de los Servicios de cuenta de Subsplash, se puede acceder a la información sobre los Servicios de cuenta de Subsplash, incluso al sitio web de Subsplash, desde fuera de Canadá o enviarla a otros fuera de Canadá. Sepa que cualquier información personal que se envíe fuera de Canadá puede estar sujeta al acceso por los agentes del orden público y las autoridades gubernamentales que tienen jurisdicción en los países en los que se encuentra la información.  

En caso de que cualquier disputa entre usted y Subsplash sobre su información personal o esta política no se resuelva dentro de treinta (30) días de acuerdo con la sección "Resolución de disputas" a continuación, cualquiera de las partes puede consultar al Comisionado de Privacidad del Canadá o a un comisionado de privacidad provincial relevante. 

**Notificación de privacidad para residentes de la UE** 

Esta Sección rige los datos personales, información recopilada para una persona física identificada o identificable, recopilados de los interesados ubicados solamente en la UE. 

**Información del Reglamento General de Protección de Datos ("GDPR" por su sigla en inglés)**

La información siguiente describe los compromisos que tenemos con usted según el Reglamento General de Protección de Datos ("GDPR") de la UE. 

El GDPR distingue entre las organizaciones que procesan datos personales para sus propósitos (conocidas como los "Responsables de los Datos" y las organizaciones que procesan datos personales a nombre de otras organizaciones (conocidas como "Procesadoras de Datos").  Subsplash solo actúa como un Responsable de los Datos para tipos de datos muy limitados, tales como la información que usted ingresa cuando registra una cuenta con nosotros o la información que envía al comprar nuestro software. Subsplash es el Responsable de los Datos de la información proporcionada por nuestros usuarios cuando proporcionamos nuestros Servicios. Subsplash es el Procesador de Datos de la información proporcionada por nuestros socios externos cuando nos brindan servicios, como cuando nuestros socios de pago procesan pagos a nombre de nuestros usuarios.

**Cuando actuamos como Controlador de Datos** 

Cuando procesamos sus datos como Controlador de Datos, corresponde lo siguiente. 

Recopilamos, usamos y compartimos sus datos personales cuando nos sentimos satisfechos de tener una base legal adecuada para hacerlo Esto puede ser porque: 

* Consentimiento: El uso que hacemos de sus datos personales está de acuerdo con su consentimiento. Si procesamos sus datos personales basados en el consentimiento, se lepedirá dicho consentimiento en o antes del momento de recopilar los datos. Puede retirar su consentimiento en cualquier momento y retirarlo no le afectará. 
* Contrato: Usamos sus datos personales para cumplir con un contrato entre usted y nosotros.
* Obligación legal: El uso que hacemos de sus datos personales es necesario para cumplir con una obligación pertinente que tenemos, legal o reglamentaria, (por ejemplo, cuando se requiere que divulguemos datos personales a un tribunal o guardemos información debido a reglamentos financieros federales); o 
* Interés legítimo: El uso que hacemos de sus datos personales es por un interés nuestro legítimo, tal como prevenir el fraude y asegurar la seguridad de nuestra red. 

Sujetos a ciertas exenciones, y en algunos casos dependiendo de la actividad de procesamiento que estamos llevando a cabo, los residentes de la UE tienen ciertos derechos en relación con sus datos personales: 

* Derecho al acceso: Usted tiene el derecho de acceder los datos personales suyos que se están procesando; específicamente, usted puede solicitar ver sus datos personales y obtener copia de los mismos. 
* El derecho a la rectificación: Usted tiene el derecho de pedir que se modifiquen sus datos personales si están incorrectos o no están actualizados. En algunas circunstancias es posible que pueda ejercer este derecho, total o parcialmente, a través de la cuenta que tiene con nosotros. 
* Derecho a ser borrado: Usted tiene el derecho de pedir que borremos sus datos personales. Sin embargo, no estamos obligados a cumplir con su solicitud de borrar sus datos personales si es necesario procesar sus datos personales para cumplir con una obligación legal o para establecer, ejercer o defender demandas legales. 
* El derecho a restringir el procesamiento En ciertas circunstancias, usted tiene el derecho de pedir la restricción del procesamiento de sus datos personales. Usted tiene el derecho de restringir el uso de sus datos personales. Sin embargo, podemos continuar el uso de sus datos personales después de una solicitud de restricción (a) cuando tengamos su consentimiento; (b) para establecer, ejercer o defender demandas legales; o (c) para proteger los derechos de otra persona física o jurídica. 
* El derecho a la portabilidad de los datos Hasta el punto en que procesemos su información (i) basados en su consentimiento o bajo contrato; y (ii) por medios automatizados, usted tiene el derecho de recibir dichos datos personales en un formato estructurado, de uso común y legible por máquina, o puede solicitar que se transfieran directamente a otra organización responsable de los datos. 
* Derecho a protestar: Usted tiene el derecho a protesttar sobre el procesamiento de sus datos personales. Sin embargo, podemos seguir procesando sus datos personales si demostramos motivos legítimos convincentes para el procesamiento que invalidan los intereses, derechos y libertades del interesado o para el establecimiento, ejercicio o defensa de demandas legales 
* El derecho a protestar el procesamiento automatizado Usted tiene el derecho de protestar las decisiones basadas en el procesamiento automatizado, tales como cuando una computadora evalúa los factores de los datos que recopilamos sobre usted y toma una decisión. Actualmente no tomamos ninguna decisión basada en el procesamiento automatizado.

Guardamos sus datos personales todo el tiempo que sea necesario para proporcionarle nuestros servicios, o para otros propósitos importantes, tales como cumplir con las obligaciones legales, resolver disputas y hacer que se cumplan nuestros acuerdos. 

Le pedimos que primero trate de resolver con nosotros cualquier problema con la protección de sus datos o solicitudes antes de ponerse en contacto con la autoridad supervisora pertinente. Si quisiera ejercer los derechos descritos anteriormente, sírvase enviar su solicitud a [\[email protected\]](https://www.subsplash.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) En su mensaje, indique el derecho que desea ejercer y la información a la que quisiera acceder, repasar, corregir o borrar. 

Le podemos pedir información adicional para confirmar su identidad, así como para la seguridad antes de divulgar los datos personales solicitados. 

Es posible que no siempre podamos abordar completamente su solicitud, por ejemplo, si tuviera un impacto en el deber de confidencialidad que debemos a otros, o si tenemos derecho legal a tratar la solicitud de una manera diferente.

**Cuando Subsplash actúa como procesador de datos** 

Cuando procesemos sus datos como Procesador de Datos, el procesamiento de sus datos no se regirá por las disposiciones anteriores ("Cuando actuamos como Controladores de Datos"), pero usted puede ponerse en contacto directo con el Controlador de Datos para saber cómo procesan su información y para ejercer sus derechos, o remitiremos su solicitud directamente a ellos a petición suya. 

El enfoque "privacidad por diseño" de Subsplash exije que nuestros niveles por defecto de la protección de datos del usuario tengan por defecto la configuración más alta. En el caso improbable de incumplimiento, Subsplash notificará a los interesados y a las Autoridades de Supervisión (SA) en la UE de acuerdo con los procedimientos dispuestos en los artículos 33 y 34 del GDPR. 

### ESTRUCTURA DEL ESCUDO DE LA PRIVACIDAD UE-EE. UU

Las siguientes disposiciones rigen la información recopilada basada en los Principios de la Estructura del Escudo de la Privacidad UE-EE. UU para las transferencias de datos personales de la UE a los Estados Unidos. Subsplash se adhiere a los Principios del Escudo de la Privacidad (los "Principios") y está comprometida a someter todos los datos personales recibidos de la UE a los Principios basados en el Escudo de la Privacidad. Las personas de las que Subsplash recopila información personal según el Escudo de la Privacidad tienen el derecho a tener acceso a sus datos personales poniéndose en contacto con Subsplash [aquí](https://www.subsplash.com/legal/data-request) o en [\[email protected\]](https://www.subsplash.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). Como resultado de la certificación al Escudo de la Privacidad, Subsplash está sujeta a los poderes de investigación y cumplimiento de la Federal Trade Commission (Comisión de Comercio de Federal) o cualquier otro organismo legal autorizado por los Estados Unidos. 

Usted puede acceder la Lista del Escudo de la Privacidad [aquí](https://www.privacyshield.gov/list).

**Notificación y opción**

Cuando Subsplash recopila información personal, puede compartir esta información con las organizaciones clientes o con terceros como se describe anteriormente en la Política de Privacidad.  Las personas deben revisar la política de privacidad de la organización cliente. Las personas tendán la opción de inscribirse o no en los servicios de Subsplash. Se proporcionará un enlace a la política de privacidad de Subsplash la primera vez que se solicite a las personas que proporcionen información personal cuando se apunten (opt-in) a los servicios de Subsplash. En los casos en que Subsplash no sea el responsable o recopilador de la información personal, solo un procesador, no tiene tiene medios para proporcionar a las personas la opción y los medios para limitar el uso y la divulgación de su información personal o proporcionarles una notificación cuando se solicita por primera vez a las personas que proporcionen información personal a Subsplash. En tales casos, Subsplash cumplirá con las instrucciones del responsable de dicha información; proporcionará medidas técnicas y de organización adecuadas para proteger los datos personales contra la destrucción accidental o ilegal o pérdida accidental, cambios, divulgación o acceso no autorizado y, hasta donde sea apropiado, ayudar al responsable a responder a las personas que están ejerciendo sus derechos según los Principios. 

En el contexto de una transferencia posterior, Subsplash tiene la responsabilidad de procesar la información personal que recibe debido al Escudo de la Privacidad y, posteriormente, la transfiere a un tercero que actúa como agente en su nombre. Subsplash continuará teniendo la 

responsabilidad civil según los Principios si su agente procesa dicha información personal de una manera inconsistente con los Principios, a menos que la organización pruebe que no es responsable del suceso que dio lugar al daño. 

**Divulgaciones a terceros**

Subsplash no divulgará información personal a terceros sin notificar a las personas que es posible que lleven a cabo dicha divulgación. En las ocasiones en que Subsplash recopile información de las personas, antes de divulgar la información personal a terceros, Subsplash les notificará a las personas el hecho de que es posible que se divulgue su información. Si las personas no desean que su información personal se divulgue a terceros, la persona no debe inscribirse para dichos servicios de Subsplash. En lo que se refiera a Subsplash Giving, la información del donante se compartirá con el Destinatario del Regalo. El Destinatario del Regalo puede utilizar un tercero con el objetivo de recibir y administrar dicha información y los donantes deben revisar las politicas de privacidad del Destinatario de Regalo respecto a esto. 

En el caso de terceros (por ejemplo, iglesias) para los que Subsplash recopila información personal, Subsplash celebrará un contrato que establece que dichos datos solo pueden procesarse con objetivos limitados y específicos consistentes con el consentimiento 

proporcionado y que dicho tercero proporcionará el mismo nivel de protección que requieren los Principios. Para los agentes destinatarios de información personal de terceros (por ejemplo, procesadores de pagos) Subsplash deberá: transferir solo datos con objetivos limitados y específicos; asegurarse de que el agente está obligado a proporcionar al menos el mismo nivel de protección de la privacidad que requieren los Principios y; al ser notificados, tomar medidas razonables y apropiadas para detener y remediar el procesamiento no autorizado. 

**Seguridad de los datos**

Subsplash tomará pasos razonables para proteger la información personal de pérdidas, uso indebido y acceso, divulgación, alteración y destrucción no autorizados. Subsplash ha puesto en práctica procedimientos físicos, electrónicos y administrativos apropiados para proteger y asegurar la información de la pérdida, el uso indebido, acceso o divulgación no autorizado, alteración o destrucción. Subsplash no puede garantizar la seguridad de la información en Internet o transmitida por Internet. 

**Integridad de los datos**

Subsplash solo procesará información personal de un modo pertinente y compatible con el objetivo para el cual fue recopilado o autorizado por aquellos que proporcionaron la información.  Hasta el punto de que sea necesario para esos objetivos, Subsplash tomará las medidas razonables para asegurar que la información personal sea correcta, esté completa, actualizada y sea confiable para el uso indicado. 

**Acceso**

En los casos en que Subsplash recopile información personal directamente de las personas, Subsplash les permitirá a esas personas el acceso a su información personal y permitirá que la persona rectifique, enmiende o borre la información incorrecta excepto cuando la carga o el gasto de proporcionar acceso estuviera fuera de proporción con los riesgos a la privacidad de la persona en el caso en cuestión o donde se violarían los derechos de otras personas. Como se indica anteriormente, usted no puede borrar toda la información si desea mantener una cuenta con Subsplash y se exije que Subsplash retenga alguna información referente a las transacciones de Subsplash Giving y los usuarios correspondientes. 

**Recursos, ejecución y responsabilidad**

**a\]** Resolución de disputas

Si usted presentó una queja a Subsplash y no se ha abordado adecuadamente, Subsplash ha designado a JAMS como el organismo independiente de resolución de disputas para abordar las quejas sobre la recopilación de información personal por Subsplash y proporcionar recursos apropiados. Dicho organismo no cobrará por sus servicios a la parte que presentó la queja. Diríjase a este [enlace](https://www.jamsadr.com/eu-us-privacy-shield) para obtener el formulario para presentar quejas al organismo independiente de resolución de disputas mencionado anteriormente.

**b\]** Arbitraje obligatorio

Si sus demandas sobre la información cubierta por el Escudo de Privacidad UE-EE. UU. no se han remediado por medio de la resolución de disputas directamente con Subsplash o por medio de la resolución de disputas independiente como se indica anteriormente, dichas "demandas residuales" pueden ser escuchadas por un "Panel del Escudo de Privacidad" compuesto por uno o tres árbitros según acuerden las partes. El Panel del Escudo de Privacidad solo puede otorgar compensación no monetaria individual, equitativa y específica (por ejemplo, acceso, corrección eliminación de los datos de la persona en cuestión) necesaria para remediar la violación de los Principios s0lo con respecto a esa persona. Es posible que no se otorguen daños, costos, gastos y otras reparaciones y cada una de las partes corre por su cuenta con sus propios honorarios de abogados. La opción del arbitraje solo está disponible para que una persona determine sobre dichas "demandas residuales", si Subsplash ha cometido con esa persona una violación de sus obligaciones según los Principios y si dicha violación sigue sin remediarse total o parcialmente.

**c\]** (GDPR) Reglamento General De Protección De Datos

El GDPR reemplaza a la Directiva 95/46/EC y tiene vigencia desde el 25 de mayo de 2018 La intención de la siguiente declaración es complementar la lo que se ha tratado anteriormente sobre el Escudo de Privacidad de la UE-EE. UU En cuanto a los datos personales recopilados y controlados por Subsplash sujetos a las calificaciones y limitaciones manifestadas en lo tratado anteriormente, los interesados de la UE conservan sus plenos derechos a ser informados de los objetivos de nuestras actividades de procesamiento al recolectar la información; de retirar el consentimiento; de acceder, rectificar, transportar y borrar sus datos personales; de oponerse al procesamiento para esfuerzos del marketing directo; y a tener objeciones cuando estén sujetos a decisiones de procesamiento automatizado. En lo que se refiere a la información personal recopilada por terceros y que Subsplash solo procesa, los interesados de la UE deben ponerse en contacto con el responsable (por ejemplo, la iglesia o ministerio) con respecto a sus derechos a ser informados de los objetivos de nuestras actividades de procesamiento en el momento de la recopilación;retirar el consentimiento; acceder, rectificar, transportar y borrar sus datos personales; oponerse al procesamiento para esfuerzos de marketing directo; y objetar cuando estén sujetos a decisiones de procesamiento automatizado. Dichos derechos pueden estar sujetos a ciertas calificaciones y limitaciones según se ha manifestado al tratar sobre el Escudo de Privacidad de la UE-EE. UU. 

Nuestros Oficiales de Procesamiento de Datos ayudarán gratis a los residentes de la UE con estas solicitudes y pueden ser contactados en [\[email protected\]](https://www.subsplash.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) 

Subsplash comprende que adoptar prácticas globales de seguridad no es una actividad que ocurra una sola vez. El enfoque "privacidad por diseño" de Subsplash exije que nuestros niveles por defecto de la protección de datos del usuario tengan por defecto la configuración más alta. En el caso improbable de incumplimiento, Subsplash notificará a los interesados y a las Autoridades de Supervisión (SA) en la UE de acuerdo con los procedimientos dispuestos en los artículos 33 y 34 del GDPR. 

Nosotros no recopilamos intencionalmente datos personales de menores y no adaptamos ningún servicio a ellos. VeraSafe ha sido nombrada representante de Subsplash en la Unión Europea para asuntos relacionados con la protección de datos según el Artículo 27 del Reglamento General de Protección de Datos de la Unión Europea. Puede ponerse en contacto con VeraSafe además de con el Funcionario de Privacidad solo para asuntos relacionados con el procesamiento de datos personales. Para hacer ese tipo de consulta, póngase en contacto con VeraSafe usando este [formulario de contacto](https://www.verasafe.com/privacy-services/contact-article-27-representative) o por teléfono llamando al: +420 228 881 031.

VeraSafe en: VeraSafe Ireland Ltd.

Unit 3D North Point House

North Point Business Park

New Mallow Road

Cork T23AT2P

Ireland

### PRIVACIDAD DE DATOS PARA RESIDENTES DE CALIFORNIA

Esta sección solo corresponde a los visitantes y usuarios de nuestro Sitio y Servicios que viven en el estado de California. Hemos adoptado esta notificación para cumplir con las leyes de privacidad llamadas "California Consumer Privacy Act" de 2018 (la "CCPA"– Ley para la privacidad del consumidor) y la California Online Privacy Protection Act (la "CalOPPA" – Ley para la protección de la privacidad en línea) y cualquier término definido en la CCPA o la CalOPPA tendrá el mismo significado cuando se use en esta notificación. 

Para los propósitos de esta sección, el "Titular de Datos de California" significará: (1) una persona que se encuentre en el estado de California para objetivos que no sean temporales o transitorios, y (2) una persona domiciliada en el estado de California que está fuera del mismo por un objetivo temporal o transitorio.

**La información que recopilamos**

Subsplash recopila información que identifica, está relacionada con, describe, se refiere a, puede estar relacionada con o pudiera estar vinculada, directa o indirectamente, con un Interesado de California o un aparato en particular ("información personal"). En particular. Subsplash ha recopilado las siguientes categorías de información personal de Interesados de California en los últimos doce (12) meses:

‍

Categoría

Ejemplos

¿Recopilamos estos datos?

Identificadores

Nombre verdadero, alias, dirección postal, identificador único personal, identificador en línea, dirección del protocolo de internet (IP), dirección de correo electrónico, nombre de la cuenta, número de seguridad social, número de licencia de conducir, número de pasaporte u otros identificadores similares.

Sí

Características de las clasificaciones protegidas bajo las leyes de California o federales.

Raza, género, identidad étnica, estado de discapacidad

No

Información comercial

Registros de propiedad personal, productos o servicios adquiridos, obtenidos o considerados u otros historiales o tendencias de adquisición o consumo.

No

Información biométrica

Huella digital, patrón facial, voz, cadencia al escribir a máquina.

Sí

Inform ación sobre la actividad en Internet o en otra red electrónica

Información sobre el uso de un sitio, software o aplicación (app).

Sí

Datos de geolocalización

Ubicación física

Sí

Información auditiva, electrónica, visual, termal, olfativa o similar

Grabaciones de un Interesado de California

Sí

Información profesional o relacionada con el empleo

Lugar de trabajo, ocupación actual, tiempo en la ocupación, posición/título

Sí

Información sobre la educación

La información que no sea identificación personal identificable disponible públicamente según se define en la ley Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA - Ley sobre derechos de una familia a la educación y la privacidad)

No

Conclusiones sacadas de cualquier información identificada arriba

Información utilizada para crear un perfil del Interesado de California que refleje sus preferencias, características, tendencias psicológicas, predisposiciones, comportamiento, actitudes, inteligencia, habilidades y aptitudes

Sí

Fuentes de información personal. Subsplash obtiene la información personal enumerada arriba de las siguientes fuentes:  

Fuente

Ejemplo

¿La recibimos de esta fuente?

Directamente de usted

De formularios que usted haya llenado o de órdenes para productos y servicios que usted compra.

Sí

Indirectamente de usted

Al observar sus acciones en el Servicio

Sí

Terceras partes

Los servicios de terceros nos proporcionan información tal como: 

* Socios de autenticación (Quienes nos pueden proporcionar información sobre los usuarios que autentican nuestros Servicios por medio de terceros) 
* Proveedores de servicios tecnológicos (Quienes nos pueden proporcionar información personal en la información sobre el uso, direcciones IP, etc. de los usuarios de nuestro Sitio y Servicios) 
* Socios de pago (Quienes nos pueden proporcionar información personal para procesar pagos de los usuarios)
* Socios publicitarios (Quienes nos pueden proporcionar información sobre los usuarios que ven nuestros anuncios)

Sí

### USO DE INFORMACIÓN PERSONAL

Podemos usar o divulgar la información personal que recopilamos para uno o más de los siguientes objetivos comerciales: 

A. Cumplir con el objetivo para el cual nos proporcionó la información. Por ejemplo, si comparte su nombre y su información de contacto para pedir una cotización o hacer una pregunta sobre nuestros productos o servicios, usaremos esa información personal para responderle. Si usted crea una cuenta en nuestros Servicios, la información personal que provee como parte del proceso puede ser visible para otros cuentahabientes y podemos usar esa información para verificar su identidad cuando acceda la cuenta. Podemos usar la información personal provista por usted para proporcionar soporte técnico. Además, podemos usar la información anterior:  

a. Para proveer, dar soporte, personalizar y desarrollar nuestros sitios web, productos y/o servicios; 

b. Para crear, mantener, personalizar y proteger la cuenta que tiene con nosotros; 

c. Para procesar sus solicitudes, compras, transacciones y pagos y prevenir el fraude en las transacciones; 

d. Para proporcionarle soporte y responder sus preguntas, incluso para investigar y abordar sus inquietudes y para monitorear y mejorar nuestras respuestas; 

e. Para ayudar a mantener la integridad y seguridad de nuestro sitio web, de los productos y servicios, las bases de datos y otras ventajas de la tecnología y las del negocio. 

f. Para responder a las solicitudes de funcionarios del órden público y según lo requiera la ley correspondiente, órden judicial o reglamentos gubernamentales; y 

g. Como le hemos descrito cuando recopilamos su información personal o como de otra manera lo indique la CCPA. 

Subsplash no recopilará, sin notificarle, otras categorías de información personal ni usará la información personal recopilada para objetivos materialmente diferentes, no relacionados o incompatibles. 

Subsplash no vende su información personal. Para proporcionarles el Servicio, Subsplash sí comparte información personal con terceros proveedores de servicios y vendedores.

### SUS DERECHOS Y SELECCIONES

Esta sección describe sus derechos bajo la CCPA y explica como ejercer dichos derechos. 

Usted tiene el derecho de solicitar que le divulguemos cierta información sobre nuestra recopilación y uso de su información personal durante los últimos 12 meses. Una vez que recibamos y verifiquemos su solicitud, le divulgaremos:

A. Las categorías de información personal recopilada sobre usted; 

B. Las categorías de las fuentes de información personal recopilada sobre usted;

C. Nuestro objetivo empresarial o comercial para recopilar o vender dicha información personal; 

D. Las categorías de terceros con los que compartimos información personal; 

E. Las partes específicas de información personal sobre usted (también llamada solicitud de portabilidad de datos); 

F. Si hemos vendido o divulgado la información personal suya con objetivos comerciales, dos listas separadas que divulguen: 

a.   las ventas, identificando las categorías de información personal que cada categoría de destinatario ha adquirido; y

b.   divulgaciones para objetivos comerciales, identificando las categorías de información personal que cada categoría de destinatario ha obtenido.

Usted tiene el derecho de pedir que borremos cualquier información personal suya que hayamos recopilado de usted y que hayamos conservado, sujeto a ciertas excepciones. Una vez que recibamos y verifiquemos su solicitud, borraremos (y ordenaremos a nuestros proveedores de servicios que la borren) su información personal de nuestros registros a menos que corresponda una excepción. 

Es posible que le neguemos la solicitud de borrarla si nosotros o nuestros proveedores de servicios necesitamos conservarla para: 

A. Completar la transacción para la que hemos recopilado información personal, proporcionar un producto o servicio solicitado por usted, actuar de un modo razonablemente anticipado dentro del contexto de nuestra continua relación comercial con usted o de otra forma cumplir con nuestro contrato con usted; 

B. Detectar incidentes de seguridad, proteger contra actividades maliciosas, engañadoras, fraudulentas o ilegales o enjuiciar a aquellos responsables de dichas actividades; 

C. Depurar productos para identificar y reparar errores que dificulten la funcionalidad existente deseada. 

D. Ejercer la libertad de expresión, asegurar el derecho de otro Interesado de California de ejercer su derecho de libertad de expresión o ejercer otro derecho provisto por la ley;Cumplir con la ley California Electronic Communications Privacy Act ((Ley de privacidad en comunicaciones electrónicas - Código penal de Cal. párrafo 1546 y siguientes.); 

E. Participar en investigaciones científicas, históricas o de estadísticas, públicas o revisadas por pares, que cumplan con todas las otras leyes éticas y de privacidad correspondientes, cuando borrar la información posiblemente pudiera imposibilitar o dificultar seriamente el logro de la investigación, si usted ha proporcionado anteriormente su consentimiento informado; 

F. Permitir solo usos internos razonablemente alineados con las expectativas del Interesado de California basada en su relación con nosotros; 

G. Cumplir con una obligación legal; y 

H. Llevar a cabo otros usos internos de esa información compatibles con el contexto en el que usted le proporcionó.

Para ejercer los derechos de acceso portabilidad de datos y supresión descritos arriba, sírvase enviarnos una solicitud del Interesado de California por correo electrónico a [\[email protected\]](https://www.subsplash.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) o llamándonos al (206) 965-8090.

Solo usted o una persona inscrita con el Secretario de Estado de California que usted autorice para actuar en su nombre puede hacer una solicitud verificable del Interesado de California relacionada con su información personal. Usted también puede hacer una solicitud del Interesado de California a nombre de su hijo(a) menor de edad. 

Usted solo puede hacer una solicitud para el acceso como Interesado de California verificable o una portabilidad de datos dos veces en un período de doce (12) meses, La solicitud del Interesado de California verificable tiene que:

A.   Proporcionar información suficiente que nos permita verificar razonablemene que usted es la persona sobre la que recopilamos información personal o es un representante autorizado de esa persona; y 

B.   Describir su solicitud con suficiente detalle que nos permita entenderla, evaluarla y responderla apropiadamente. 

No podemos responder a su solicitud ni proporcionarle la información personal si no podemos verificar su identidad o autoridad para hacer dicha solicitud y confirmar la información personal relacionada con usted. Hacer una solicitud como un Interesado de California verificable no exige crear una cuenta con nosotros. Solo usaremos la información personal proporcionada en la solicitud de un Interesado de California verificable para verificar la identidad del solicitante o la autoridad para solicitarla. 

Aspiramos responder a una solicitud de un Interesado de California verificable dentro de cuarenta y cinco (45) días de haber verificado dicha solicitud. Si necesitamos más tiempo (hasta noventa (90) días) le informaremos la razón o razones por las que necesitamos una extensión y cuánto tiempo anticipamos que tomará. Cualquier divulgación proporcionada solo cubrirá el período de doce (12) meses previos a la recepción de su solicitud Si corresponde, es posible que la respuesta le proporcione las razones por las que no podemos cumplir con su solicitud. Para las solicitudes de portabilidad de datos, seleccionaremos un formato para darle la información personal que se pueda usar fácilmente y le pudiera permitir la transmisión de la información de una entidad a otra sin obstáculos. No cobramos por procesar ni por responder a su solicitud verificable de Interesado de California a menos que sea escesiva, repetitiva o evidentemente infundada. Si determinamos que la solicitud justifica un cargo, le diremos porqué tomamos esa decisión y le proporcionaremos un cálculo del precio antes de completar su solicitud. Nos reservamos del derecho a rechazar la respuesta a un Interesado de California verificable que sean excesivas, repetitivas o evidentemente infundadas. 

### EL DERECHO A NO SER DISCRIMINADO  

No le discriminaremos por ejercer ninguno de los derechos de la CCPA. No actuaremos contra usted de ninguna de las formas siguientes para responder al ejercicio de sus derechos. 

1\. Denegarle bienes o servicios.

2\. Cobrarle un precio o tarifa diferente por los bienes o servicios, incluso con descuentos u otros beneficios, o imponiéndole penalidades.  

3\. Proporcionarle bienes o servicios con un nivel o calidad diferente.

4\. Sugerirle que puede recibir un precio o tarifa diferente por los bienes o servicios o un nivel o calidad diferente de bienes o servicios. 

### DIVULGACIONES DE LA CLÁUSULA "DO NOT TRACK" (NO HACER SEGUIMIENTO) DE CALIFORNIA (DNT) 

Subsplash no le hace seguimiento a sus clientes a través del tiempo y con sitios web de terceros para proporcionar publicidad orientada a grupos específicos y, por lo tanto, no responde a las señales de Do Not Track (DNT -No hacer seguimiento) Los terceros que hayan insertado contenido en los sitios web, software o aplicaciones móviles (por ej. características sociales) de Subsplash pueden usar cookies en el navegador del usuario y/u obtener información sobre el hecho de que un navegador web visitó un sitio web específico de Subsplash desde cierta dirección IP. Terceras partes no pueden recopilar ninguna otra información personal identificable de los sitios web de Subsplash a menos que usted se la proporcione a ellos directamente. 

### INFORMACIÓN ESPECIAL PARA LOS RESIDENTES DE NEVADA 

Los residentes del Estado de Nevada tienen el derecho de rechazar la venta de ciertas partes de su información a otras empresas que venderán o licenciarán su información a otros. Subsplash no vende ni alquila su información de contacto a otros comerciantes o a ningún otro tercero. Si usted es residente de Nevada y tiene preguntas adicionales contáctenos [aquí](https://www.subsplash.com/legal/data-request) o por correo electrónico a [\[email protected\]](https://www.subsplash.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

### CAMPAÑAS ESPECIALIZADAS DE SOCIOS 

De vez en cuando, Subsplash puede trabajar con organizaciones asociadas para desarrollar y distribuir contenidos especializados. Los usuarios que participen en las campañas de marketing especializadas completando nuestro formulario de contacto y descargando el contenido correspondiente, estarán sujetos a la Notificación Suplementaria de Privacidad, además de la presente Política de Privacidad.

### EL COMPROMISO DE TODA NUESTRA EMPRESA CON SU PRIVACIDAD 

Para asegurarnos que su información personal está segura, les comunicamos estas pautas de privacidad a los empleados de Subsplash y hacemos que en la compañia se cumpla estrictamente la protección a su privacidad. 

### SOLICITUDES DE LIBERTAD DE INFORMACIÓN 

Si se está comunicando o haciendo un donativo a cualquier organización o institución que esté sujeta a la legislación de "libertad de información" o "acceso a la información" del sector público federal o provincial, fíjese que la información relacionada con su comunicación y/o donativo puede divulgarse a terceros de acuerdo con los procedimientos disponibles según esas leyes. 

### CONSULTAS, QUEJAS Y RESOLUCIÓN DE DISPUTAS 

Si quiere verificar, corregir o borrar cualquier información personal que hayamos recopilado, o si tiene alguna pregunta o inquietud, o si tiene alguna queja, contáctenos [aquí](https://www.subsplash.com/legal/data-request) o por correo electrónico en [\[email protected\]](https://www.subsplash.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). Si hay una disputa entre usted y Subsplash en lo que refiere a su información personal o a esta política, usted acepta hacer todo esfuerzo razonable para resolver dicha disputa con Subsplash de manera informal y consultar y negociar con Subsplash de buena fe para llegar a una solución justa y equitativa.

### PREGUNTAS SOBRE LA PRIVACIDAD 

Si tiene preguntas o inquietudes sobre la política de privacidad de Subsplash, sírvase ponerse en contacto con nuestro Oficial de Privacidad. Se puede poner en contacto con nuestro Oficial de Privacidad en: 

Subsplash, Inc.

750 N Saint Paul St Ste 250, PMB 41141, Dallas, Texas 75201-3206

Email: [\[email protected\]](https://www.subsplash.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

### ‍

Dernière mise à jour le 27 septembre 2022 – Version 4.6

La présente politique de protection de la vie privée décrit la collecte, l’utilisation, la protection, la divulgation, la correction et la suppression de vos Informations à caractère personnel par Subsplash. Veuillez prendre le temps de lire ce qui suit afin d’en savoir plus sur nos pratiques en matière d’informations, notamment le type d’informations qui sont recueillies, comment elles sont utilisées et à quelles fins, à qui nous divulguons ces informations et de quelle façon nous protégeons vos Informations à caractère personnel. La protection de votre vie privée est une priorité chez Subsplash, et nous faisons beaucoup d’efforts pour la protéger.

La présente politique de protection de la vie privée s’applique aux sites Web hébergés sur subsplash.com et thechurchapp.com, y compris toutes les pages secondaires et les nouvelles versions de ces pages, ainsi que tous les logiciels et services que nous offrons, y compris notamment les services que nous offrons par le biais de nos sites Web lorsque vous vous inscrivez à un compte Subsplash (collectivement appelés les « Services de compte Subsplash »).

Subsplash peut de temps à autre mettre à jour sa politique de protection de la vie privée. Lorsque nous modifions la politique de façon importante, un avis est affiché sur notre site Web avec la politique de protection de la vie privée actualisée.

### POURQUOI RECUEILLONS-NOUS DES INFORMATIONS À CARACTÈRE PERSONNEL

Nous recueillons des Informations à caractère personnel pour les raisons suivantes:

* Elles aident Subsplash à fournir et à gérer vos Services de compte Subsplash
* Elles aident Subsplash à fournir à la clientèle un service de qualité supérieure
* Elles permettent à Subsplash de vous donner un accès pratique à nos produits et services et de mettre l’accent sur les catégories les plus intéressantes pour vous
* Elles aident Subsplash à vous tenir informé des dernières annonces de produits, des mises à jour logicielles, des offres spéciales et des événements susceptibles de vous intéresser. Si vous ne souhaitez pas que Subsplash vous informe des actualités, des mises à jour logicielles et des plus récentes informations sur les produits et services de Subsplash, veuillez soumettre votre demande [ici](https://www.subsplash.com/legal/data-request) ou nous envoyer un courrier électronique à l’adresse [\[email protected\]](https://www.subsplash.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

### QUELLES INFORMATIONS RECUEILLONS-NOUS, À QUEL MOMENT ET COMMENT POUVONS-NOUS LES UTILISER

Si vous souhaitez utiliser les Services de compte Subsplash, Subsplash a besoin de vos informations aux fins de traitement et de transmission des informations pour véhiculer les données et contenu adéquats entre les serveurs et les applications et vous assurer ainsi une bonne expérience.

Il y a également certaines situations pour lesquelles vos Informations à caractère personnel peuvent nous aider à vous offrir un meilleur service. Par exemple:

* Nous pouvons vous demander vos Informations à caractère personnel lorsque vous parlez au téléphone avec l’un de nos collaborateurs au sujet d’un problème de service, que vous téléchargez une mise à jour logicielle, que vous vous inscrivez à un séminaire, que vous participez à un enquête en ligne, que vous enregistrez vos produits ou que vous achetez un produit
* Lors de votre interaction avec Subsplash, nous pouvons recueillir des Informations à caractère personnel pertinentes à la situation, comme votre nom, votre adresse postale, votre numéro de téléphone, votre courrier électronique et votre mode de contact de préférence, les informations de votre carte de crédit et les informations concernant les produits Subsplash que vous possédez, comme leurs numéros de série et leur date d’achat, et les informations concernant un problème de support ou de service
* Nous recueillons des informations concernant les activités de nos clients sur nos sites Web et nos applications. Cela nous aide à déterminer comment fournir au mieux des informations pertinentes aux clients et à comprendre quelles parties de nos sites Web, quels produits et services Internet sont les plus intéressants pour eux, ainsi qu’à diagnostiquer des problèmes avec nos services et nos sites Web
* Lorsque vous visitez l’application mobile Subsplash, nous pouvons vous demander de consentir à nous permettre d’utiliser la technologie GPS (ou une autre technologie similaire) pour déterminer votre position actuelle aux fins de production de rapports sur l’activité et l’engagement des utilisateurs. Si vous ne voulez pas que nous utilisions votre localisation aux fins susmentionnées, il vous faut ne pas y consentir ou alors désactiver les services de localisation pour l’application mobile Subsplash situés dans les réglages de votre compte, dans les réglages de votre téléphone portable ou dans l’application mobile;
* Nous pouvons utiliser des Informations à caractère personnel pour fournir des produits et/ou des services que vous avez demandés, ainsi qu’à des fins d’audit, de recherche et d’analyse pour améliorer les produits Subsplash
* Si vous utilisez la fonctionnalité de messagerie Subsplash, Subsplash stocke le contenu de vos messages, qui peuvent contenir des Informations à caractère personnel, et ainsi obtenir le numéro de votre appareil portable ou votre adresse électronique et demander l’accès aux contacts de votre appareil portable afin d’accéder seulement au numéro de téléphone et/ou à l’adresse électronique des personnes en particulier que vous choisissez de contacter par le service de messagerie et de stocker ces informations – Subsplash ne copiera aucune coordonnée de personnes avec qui vous ne communiquez pas à l’aide du service de messagerie. En ce qui concerne les coordonnées des personnes particulières que vous contactez à l’aide du service de messagerie, Subsplash n’utilisera ces informations que dans le but de fournir le service et ne les utilisera à aucune autre fin
* Si vous vous inscrivez à la messagerie Subsplash, telle que décrite ci-dessus, et que vous choisissez d’inviter d’autres utilisateurs à se joindre à une conversation, Subsplash demandera l’accès à vos contacts, même si ce n’est pas obligatoire pour inviter d’autres utilisateurs à votre conversation. Subsplash n’utilisera cet accès que pour vous permettre d’inviter d’autres utilisateurs
* Subsplash peut utiliser des formes agrégées et anonymes d’Informations à caractère personnel à diverses fins, notamment pour analyser les tendances de l’usage, la détection de fraude et l’élaboration de nouveaux services.

### LES INFORMATIONS AFFICHÉES PUBLIQUEMENT SONT PUBLIQUES 

Si vous utilisez un tableau d’affichage, un service de diffusion en continu ou un espace de chat sur un site Web ou un service Subsplash, sachez que toute information que vous partagez est visible par d’autres utilisateurs. Les renseignements permettant de vous identifier que vous soumettez sur l’un de ces forums peuvent être lus, recueillis ou utilisés par quiconque pour vous envoyer des messages non sollicités. Subsplash n’est pas responsable des renseignements permettant de vous identifier que vous choisissez de soumettre sur ces forums. Par exemple, si vous choisissez de rendre publique une information qui était auparavant non publique, en la révélant dans ces forums ou en autorisant certaines fonctionnalités d’utilisateur, Subsplash recueillera cette information de votre interaction et l’information sera rendue publique.

### QUAND DIVULGUONS-NOUS VOS INFORMATIONS

Subsplash prend la protection de votre vie privée très au sérieux. Subsplash ne vend pas et ne loue pas vos coordonnées à d’autres spécialistes du marketing ni à aucun autre tiers. Si vous souhaitez utiliser les Services de compte Subsplash, Subsplash divulgue vos informations aux institutions et aux prestataires de services tiers aux fins de traitement et de transmission des informations pour véhiculer les données et contenu adéquats entre les serveurs et les applications et vous assurer ainsi une bonne expérience. Si vous invitez d’autres utilisateurs sur l’un de nos services, nous pouvons dire à la ou aux personnes que vous invitez qui les a invitées. Subsplash peut partager avec des tiers des formes agrégées et anonymes d’Informations à caractère personnel et, dans ce cas, les informations partagées le seront sous une forme dépersonnalisée et non identifiable.

### AU SEIN DU GROUPE SUBSPLASH

Subsplash, Inc. et Subsplash Wallet, LLC exercent toutes deux leurs activités sous le nom de « Subsplash » et en tant que groupe. Pour nous aider à offrir un service supérieur, vos Informations à caractère personnel peuvent être partagées avec des personnes morales du groupe Subsplash au niveau mondial, qui prendra des mesures raisonnables pour les protéger conformément à la politique de protection de la vie privée de Subsplash.

### AVEC NOS PRESTATAIRES DE SERVICES, SOUS-TRAITANTS ET PARTENAIRES STRATÉGIQUES

Il y a aussi des moments où il peut être avantageux pour Subsplash de mettre certaines de vos Informations à caractère personnel à la disposition d’entreprises avec qui Subsplash entretient une relation stratégique ou qui exécutent des travaux pour Subsplash afin de fournir des produits et services en notre nom. Ces entreprises peuvent nous aider à traiter les informations, à accorder un crédit, à exécuter les commandes des clients, à vous livrer des produits, à gérer et à améliorer les données clientèle, à assurer le service à la clientèle, à évaluer votre intérêt pour nos produits et services, ou à effectuer des recherches sur la clientèle ou des enquêtes de satisfaction. Ces entreprises sont également tenues de protéger vos Informations à caractère personnel en stricte conformité avec les politiques de Subsplash, sauf si nous vous indiquons le contraire au moment de la collecte. Sans la mise à disposition de ces informations, il vous serait difficile d’acheter nos produits, que ces produits vous soient livrés, de recevoir un service à la clientèle, de nous faire part de vos commentaires pour améliorer nos produits et services, ou d’avoir accès à certains services, offres ou contenu sur le site Web de Subsplash.

### PROMOTIONS PARTENAIRES

Nous pouvons proposer des concours, loteries ou autres promotions avec des partenaires tiers. Si vous décidez de participer à un concours, une loterie ou autre promotion parrainé(e) et/ou en association avec un partenaire tiers, les informations que vous fournissez seront partagées avec nous et avec eux. Leur utilisation de vos informations n'est pas régie par la présente Politique de protection de la vie privée.

### TRANSFERTS D'ENTREPRISES

Nous pouvons choisir d'acheter ou de vendre des actifs et pouvons partager et/ou transférer des informations clients, y compris des Informations à caractère personnel, dans le cadre de l'évaluation et de la conclusion de ces opérations et sur la base de nos intérêts légitimes. En outre, si nos actifs ou nous sommes rachetés, si nous cessons nos activités, si nous faisons faillite ou si nous subissons un changement de contrôle, les Informations à caractère personnel peuvent être l'un des actifs transférés ou rachetés par un tiers.

### REQUÊTES LÉGALES

Parfois, la loi ou un litige peut nous contraindre à divulguer vos Informations à caractère personnel. Nous pouvons aussi divulguer des informations à votre sujet si nous déterminons de façon raisonnable que la divulgation est nécessaire pour des raisons de sécurité nationale, d’application de la loi ou d’autres questions d’importance publique.

### SUBSPLASH GIVING

Subsplash Giving est une fonctionnalité connectée à Internet qui peut être utilisée sur un navigateur Web et des appareils mobiles. Elle a été élaborée par Subsplash pour permettre aux donateurs de faire des dons d’argent à des organisations tierces. Si vous choisissez d’utiliser la fonctionnalité Subsplash Giving pour faire des dons, Subsplash et l’organisme de traitement des paiements recueilleront des Informations à caractère personnel à votre sujet, y compris votre nom, vos coordonnées, les sommes des dons, et l’organisme de traitement des paiements recevra certaines informations sur le paiement (p. ex. numéro de carte de crédit, adresse de facturation, code de sécurité) et utilisera ces informations pour traiter les paiements et vous fournir des relevés de transaction. Les informations du donateur seront partagées avec le bénéficiaire du don.

Lorsque vous envoyez un SMS à Subsplash ou à Subsplash Wallet dans le but d’utiliser la fonctionnalité de dons par SMS, vous divulguez votre numéro de téléphone portable à Subsplash, Inc., et vous consentez par conséquent à recevoir par SMS un hyperlien vers le portail de dons Subsplash Wallet. Pour cesser de recevoir des SMS de Subsplash ou de Subsplash Wallet, répondez au SMS en tapant « STOP ».

### SUBSPLASH LIVE

Subsplash Live utilise les services API de YouTube, régis par les Règles de protection de la vie privée de Google ([https://policies.google.com/privacy](https://policies.google.com/privacy)), pour accéder au nom de chaîne YouTube et à l’identifiant de votre organisation, ainsi que pour créer des diffusions de vidéo et des radiodiffusions en direct au nom de votre organisation. Nous faisons cela pour afficher la chaîne liée dans votre tableau de bord Subsplash et pour créer des radiodiffusions en direct groupées sur cette chaîne. En plus de la procédure normale de Subsplash pour supprimer les données stockées, votre organisation peut révoquer l’accès de Subsplash Live à vos données YouTube par le biais de la page des réglages de sécurité Google ([https://security.google.com/settings/security/permissions](https://security.google.com/settings/security/permissions)). Veuillez contacter Subsplash pour toute question ou plainte au sujet des pratiques de protection de la vie privée de Subsplash Live.

### COOKIES ET AUTRES TECHNOLOGIES

Comme cela est pratique courante sur de nombreux sites Web d’entreprises, les sites Web de Subsplash utilisent des « cookies » et d’autres technologies pour nous aider à comprendre quelles parties de nos sites Web sont les plus populaires, où vont les visiteurs et le temps qu’ils y passent. Nous utilisons aussi des cookies et d’autres technologies pour nous assurer que nos publicités en ligne attirent des clients vers nos produits et services. Les cookies contiennent des informations qui sont transférées sur le disque dur de votre ordinateur. Ces cookies servent à stocker des informations comme l’heure à laquelle la visite en cours a lieu, si le visiteur est déjà venu sur le site auparavant et quel site a renvoyé le visiteur à la page Web.

Cependant, si vous préférez ne pas autoriser les cookies, vous pouvez les désactiver dans votre navigateur. Veuillez noter que certaines fonctionnalités des sites Web de Subsplash et certains produits en ligne de Subsplash ne seront pas disponibles si les cookies sont désactivés. Comme c’est le cas de la plupart des sites Web, nous recueillons automatiquement certaines informations et les stockons dans des fichiers journaux. Ces informations sont, entre autres, les adresses de protocole Internet (IP), le type de navigateur, le fournisseur d’accès à Internet (FAI), les pages de renvoi ou de sortie, le système d’exploitation, l’estampille date/heure et les données du flux de clics. Nous pouvons également suivre les données liées à l’utilisation, comme la fréquence à laquelle vous visitez notre site ou utilisez nos applications, combien de messages vous envoyez et la façon dont vous utilisez notre contenu.

Nous utilisons aussi Google Analytics. Google Analytics est un outil d’analyse Web qui aide les propriétaires de sites Web à comprendre comment les utilisateurs utilisent leur site Web.  

Comme la plupart des services, Google Analytics utilise des cookies internes pour suivre les interactions des visiteurs comme dans notre cas, où ils servent à recueillir des informations au sujet de la façon dont les visiteurs utilisent notre site. Nous utilisons ensuite les informations pour compiler des rapports et nous aider à améliorer notre site.

Nous pouvons aussi utiliser d’autres outils de Google Analytics, comme leur outil de données démographiques et centres d’intérêt qui nous permet d’en apprendre davantage sur les caractéristiques et les intérêts des utilisateurs qui visitent notre site Web, ou leur outil de remarketing, qui nous permet de placer des publicités pertinentes sur différents sites Web et services en ligne.

Google Analytics recueille des informations de façon anonyme et produit des rapports sur les tendances des sites Web sans identifier les visiteurs individuels. Vous pouvez désactiver Google Analytics sans que cela affecte la façon dont vous visitez notre site – pour obtenir plus d’information sur la désactivation du suivi par Google Analytics sur les sites Web que vous utilisez, consultez cette [page Google](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

Nous utilisons ces informations pour analyser les tendances, gérer le site, suivre les mouvements des utilisateurs sur le site et recueillir des informations démographiques au sujet de notre base d’utilisateurs dans son ensemble.

Dans certains de nos courriers électroniques, nous nous servons d’un lien « URL de clic » lié au contenu sur le site Web de Subsplash. Lorsque les clients cliquent sur l’un de ces liens URL, ils passent par le serveur de notre site Web avant d’arriver à la page de destination. Nous suivons ces données de clics pour nous aider à déterminer l’intérêt pour des sujets précis et mesurer l’efficacité de nos communications avec nos clients. Si vous préférez ne pas faire l’objet d’un suivi, évitez simplement de cliquer sur les liens textuels ou graphiques dans les courriers électroniques. En outre, nous utilisons des pixels invisibles – de minuscules images graphiques – pour nous indiquer quelles parties de notre site Web les clients ont visitées ou pour mesurer l’efficacité des recherches effectuées par les clients sur notre site.

Les pixels invisibles nous permettent aussi d’envoyer des courriers électroniques dans un format que les clients peuvent lire. Et ces pixels nous indiquent si les courriers électroniques ont été ouverts pour nous assurer que nous n’envoyons que des messages qui ont de l’intérêt pour nos clients. Nous pouvons utiliser ces informations pour réduire ou éliminer les messages envoyés au client.

### COMMENT NOUS PROTÉGEONS VOS INFORMATIONS À CARACTÈRE PERSONNEL

Subsplash prend des précautions – y compris des mesures administratives, techniques et physiques – pour protéger vos Informations à caractère personnel contre la perte, le vol et l’usage abusif, ainsi que l’accès, la divulgation, l’altération et la destruction non autorisés. Les sites Web de Subsplash utilisent le chiffrement par couche de sockets sécurisée (protocole SSL) sur toutes les pages Web où des Informations à caractère personnel sont requises. Pour effectuer des achats sur la boutique en ligne de Subsplash ou par le biais de vos comptes Subsplash, vous devez utiliser un navigateur qui autorise le protocole SSL, comme Safari, Google ou Internet Explorer. Vous protégez ainsi la confidentialité de vos Informations à caractère personnel et de vos cartes de crédit lors de leur transmission sur Internet. Vous pouvez nous aider en prenant des précautions pour protéger vos données à caractère personnel lorsque vous êtes sur Internet. Modifiez souvent vos mots de passe en utilisant une combinaison de lettres et de chiffres, et assurez-vous d’utiliser un navigateur Web sûr comme Safari ou Google.  

### INTÉGRITÉ DE VOS INFORMATIONS À CARACTÈRE PERSONNEL

Subsplash vous permet de conserver vos Informations à caractère personnel exactes, complètes et à jour. Naturellement, vous avez le droit d’accéder aux Informations à caractère personnel que vous avez fournies, de les corriger et de les supprimer, même si vous ne pouvez pas supprimer toutes les informations si vous voulez maintenir un compte Subsplash et que Subsplash a l’obligation de conserver certaines informations concernant les transactions et les donateurs de Subsplash Giving. En dépit de nos efforts sincères, des erreurs surviennent parfois. Si vous trouvez une quelconque information personnelle qui est périmée, inexacte ou incomplète, indiquez-le-nous, nous effectuerons les corrections rapidement et nous ferons tous les efforts nécessaires pour communiquer ces changements à d’autres parties qui pourraient avoir reçu par inadvertance de notre part des Informations à caractère personnel inexactes ou périmées. Si vous supprimez vos informations, cette suppression peut empêcher Subsplash de continuer à vous offrir certains ou tous les services de compte Subsplash.

Subsplash ne conserve les Informations à caractère personnel que tant que nous sommes dans l’obligation de le faire pour notre relation d’affaires ou comme l’exigent des lois fédérales, d’État ou provinciales, sous réserve des pratiques raisonnables de l’industrie en matière de conservation de documents. Subsplash a des procédures adéquates en place concernant la destruction, la suppression et l’élimination des Informations à caractère personnel lorsqu’elles ne sont plus requises par Subsplash, sous réserve des lois applicables.  

### ENFANTS

Subsplash reconnaît que les parents, tuteurs et autres adultes achètent souvent nos produits en vue d’une utilisation familiale, y compris une utilisation par des mineurs. Nous ne recueillons pas sciemment d’Informations à caractère personnel concernant des enfants âgés de moins de 13 ans à des fins commerciales, mais comme certaines informations sont recueillies par voie électronique, elles peuvent apparaître comme étant les Informations à caractère personnel de l’acheteur Subsplash du produit et elles seront traitées comme telles par la présente politique de protection de la vie privée. Si un enfant de moins de 13 ans soumet des Informations à caractère personnel à Subsplash sans le consentement d’un parent ou d’un tuteur et que nous apprenons que ces informations sont celles d’un enfant de moins de 13 ans, nous supprimerons les informations dès que possible.

Jamais nous ne partagerons, vendrons, louerons ou transférerons les Informations à caractère personnel d’un enfant autrement que selon la description de la présente section.

Nous pouvons divulguer des informations agrégées au sujet d’un grand nombre de nos utilisateurs qui peuvent comprendre des informations agrégées qui n’identifient personne en particulier. En outre, nous pouvons divulguer les Informations à caractère personnel d’enfants:

* À des tiers que le parent ou tuteur a approuvés par le biais des services

* Si nous sommes contraints de le faire par la loi ou une procédure judiciaire, comme pour nous conformer à tout ordre d’un tribunal ou toute assignation à comparaître, ou pour répondre à toute demande gouvernementale ou règlementaire
* Si nous croyons que la divulgation est nécessaire ou appropriée pour protéger les droits, la propriété ou la sécurité de Subsplash, de nos clients ou d’autres personnes, notamment pour : 1) protéger la sécurité d’un enfant; 2) protéger la sûreté et la sécurité des services; ou 3) nous permettre de prendre des précautions en matière de responsabilité. 
* Aux organismes d’application de la loi ou pour une enquête relative à la sécurité publique.

Vous pouvez à tout moment examiner les Informations à caractère personnel de votre enfant que nous conservons, nous demander de corriger ou de supprimer ces informations et/ou refuser de nous permettre de continuer à en recueillir ou d’utiliser les informations de l’enfant.

Vous pouvez examiner, modifier ou supprimer les Informations à caractère personnel de votre enfant en:

* Vous connectant à votre compte ou en
* Soumettant une demande [ici](https://subsplash.com/legal/data-request) ou en nous envoyant un courrier électronique à l’adresse [\[email protected\]](https://www.subsplash.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). Pour protéger votre vie privée et votre sécurité, nous pouvons vous demander d’effectuer certaines démarches ou de fournir des informations supplémentaires pour vérifier votre identité avant de vous donner une quelconque information ou d’apporter des corrections.

### CLIENTS CANADIENS

Nos politiques et pratiques ont été conçues de manière à être conformes à la Loi sur la protection des renseignements personnels et les documents électroniques (Canada), à la Loi sur la protection des renseignements personnels (Canada) et à toutes les lois provinciales qui réglementent le traitement des renseignements personnels dans les secteurs privé et public.

 Selon le lieu où se trouvent les utilisateurs des Services de compte Subsplash, il peut être possible d’avoir accès aux informations sur les Services de compte Subsplash, y compris le site Web de Subsplash, hors du Canada ou de pouvoir les envoyer à d’autres personnes hors du Canada. Veuillez noter que pour toute information personnelle qui est envoyée hors du Canada, un accès peut être octroyé aux services d’application de la loi et aux autorités gouvernementales ayant compétence dans les pays où l’information est située.

Dans le cas où un différend entre vous et Subsplash au sujet de vos Informations à caractère personnel ou de la présente politique n’est pas résolu conformément à la section « Règlement des différends » ci-après  dans les trente (30) jours, l’une ou l’autre des parties peut consulter le commissaire à la protection de la vie privée du Canada ou un commissaire à la protection de la vie privée provincial pertinent.

Avis de protection de la vie privée pour les résidents de l’UE

La présente section régit les données à caractère personnel concernant une personne physique identifiée ou identifiable, uniquement recueillies auprès de personnes situées dans l’Union européenne (UE).

Information sur le Règlement général sur la protection des données (« GDPR »)

L’information qui suit décrit nos engagements envers vous en vertu du Règlement général sur la protection des données (« GDPR ») de l’UE.

Le GDPR fait la distinction entre les organisations qui traitent des données à caractère personnel à des fins qui leur sont propres (connues comme étant des « responsables de traitement des données ») et celles qui traitent des données à caractère personnel pour le compte d’autres organisations (connues comme étant des « prestataires de services de traitement de données »). Subsplash agit uniquement comme responsable de traitement de données pour des types très limités de données, comme les informations que vous saisissez lorsque vous ouvrez un compte chez nous ou les informations que vous soumettez lorsque vous achetez notre logiciel. Subsplash est le responsable de traitement de données pour les informations données par nos utilisateurs lorsque nous fournissons nos services. Subsplash est le prestataire de services de traitement de données pour les informations données par nos partenaires tiers lorsqu’ils nous fournissent des services, tels que nos partenaires de paiement qui traitent les paiements au nom de nos utilisateurs.

Quand agissons-nous en qualité de responsable de traitement de données

Lorsque nous traitons vos données en tant que responsable de traitement de données, les règles suivantes s’appliquent. 

Nous recueillons, utilisons et partageons vos données à caractère personnel lorsque nous sommes convaincus que nous disposons de la base juridique appropriée pour le faire. Cela peut être: 

* Par consentement : notre utilisation de vos données à caractère personnel est conforme à votre consentement. Si nous traitons vos données à caractère personnel en fonction de votre consentement, nous vous demanderont ce consentement au moment ou avant la collecte de données. Vous pouvez retirer votre consentement à tout moment et ne subirez aucun préjudice pour avoir retiré votre consentement.
* Par contrat : notre utilisation de vos données à caractère personnel sert à honorer un contrat entre vous et nous.
* Par obligation légale : notre utilisation de vos données à caractère personnel est nécessaire pour nous conformer à une obligation légale ou réglementaire que nous avons (par exemple, lorsque nous sommes obligés de divulguer des données à caractère personnel à un tribunal ou de stocker des informations en raison de règlements financiers fédéraux).
* Par intérêt légitime : notre utilisation de vos données à caractère personnel est d’un intérêt légitime pour nous, comme prévenir la fraude et assurer la sécurité de notre réseau.

Sous réserve de certaines exceptions et dans certains cas, selon l'activité de traitement, les résidents de l’UE ont certains droits en ce qui concerne leurs données à caractère personnel: 

* Droit d’accès : vous avez le droit d’accès à vos données à caractère personnel lorsqu’elles sont traitées ; vous pouvez en particulier demander de voir vos données à caractère personnel et obtenir des copies de vos données à caractère personnel.
* Droit de rectification : vous avez le droit de demander des modifications à vos données à caractère personnel si elles sont périmées ou inexactes. Dans certaines circonstances, vous pouvez exercer ce droit, en tout ou en partie, par le biais de votre compte existant chez nous.
* Droit à l’effacement : vous avez le droit de demander que nous supprimions vos données à caractère personnel. Cependant, nous ne sommes pas tenus de nous conformer à votre demande d’effacement de vos données à caractère personnel si le traitement de vos données à caractère personnel est nécessaire pour nous conformer à une obligation légale ou en vue de la constatation, de l’exercice ou de la défense de droits en justice.
* Droit à la limitation du traitement : dans certaines circonstances, vous avez le droit de demander une limitation du traitement de vos données à caractère personnel. Vous avez le droit de limiter l’utilisation de vos données à caractère personnel. Cependant, nous pouvons continuer à utiliser vos données à caractère personnel après une demande de limitation a) lorsque nous avons votre consentement; b) pour la constatation, l’exercice ou la défense de droits en justice ou c) pour la protection des droits d’une autre personne physique ou morale.
* Droit à la portabilité des données : dans la mesure où nous traitons vos informations i) sur la base de votre consentement ou dans le cadre d’un contrat et ii) par des moyens automatisés, vous avez le droit de recevoir ces données à caractère personnel dans un format structuré, couramment utilisé et lisible par une machine ou vous pouvez demander qu’elles soient transmises directement à un autre responsable de traitement des données.
* Droit d’opposition : vous avez le droit de vous opposer au traitement de vos données à caractère personnel. Toutefois, nous pourrons encore traiter vos données si nous démontrons qu’il existe des motifs légitimes et impérieux pour le traitement qui prévalent sur les intérêts, les droits et les libertés de la personne concernée ou pour la constatation, l’exercice ou la défense de droits en justice.
* Droit de s’opposer au traitement automatisé : vous avez le droit de vous opposer à faire l’objet d’une décision fondée sur un traitement automatisé, comme lorsqu’un ordinateur évalue des facteurs dans les données que nous recueillons à votre sujet et prend une décision. Nous ne prenons actuellement aucune décision fondée sur un traitement automatisé. 

Nous conservons vos données à caractère personnel aussi longtemps que nécessaire pour vous fournir nos services, ou à d’autres fins importantes, comme celles de nous conformer à des obligations légales, de régler des différends et d’imposer le respect de nos accords. 

Nous vous demandons de bien vouloir tenter de résoudre tout problème concernant la protection de vos données ou nous demander de le faire avant de contacter l’autorité de contrôle pertinente. Si vous souhaitez exercer l’un des droits décrits ci-dessus, veuillez en envoyer la demande à l’adresse [\[email protected\]](https://www.subsplash.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). Veuillez indiquer dans votre message le droit que vous souhaitez exercer et les informations que vous souhaitez consulter, réviser, corriger ou supprimer.

Nous pouvons vous demander des informations supplémentaires pour confirmer votre identité et à des fins de sécurité avant de divulguer les données à caractère personnel demandées.

Il se peut que nous ne soyons pas toujours pleinement en mesure de répondre à votre demande, par exemple si cela affecterait le devoir de protection de la vie privée que nous avons envers les autres ou si nous sommes légalement autorisés à traiter la demande d’une manière différente.

Lorsque Subsplash agit comme prestataire de services de traitement des données

Lorsque nous traitons vos données en notre qualité de prestataire de services de traitement des données, le traitement de vos données ne sera pas régi par les dispositions qui précèdent (« Lorsque nous agissons comme responsable des données »), mais vous pouvez contacter directement le responsable des données pour connaître son traitement de vos informations et pour exercer vos droits, ou nous leur transmettrons directement votre demande, si vous nous le demandez.

L’approche de Subsplash basée sur la protection de la vie privée dès la conception {« privacy by design ») exige que les niveaux de protection des données de nos utilisateurs soient automatiquement réglés par défaut au niveau le plus élevé. Dans le cas peu probable d’une violation de données à caractère personnel, Subsplash avisera les personnes concernées et les autorités de contrôle de l’UE selon les procédures indiquées aux Articles 33 et 34 du GDPR.  

### CADRE DU BOUCLIER DE PROTECTION DES DONNÉES  (« PRIVACY SHIELD ») UE–USA

Les dispositions suivantes régissent les informations recueillies en s’appuyant sur les principes du Privacy Shield UE–USA pour les transferts de données à caractère personnel de l’UE vers les États-Unis. Subsplash adhère aux principes du Privacy Shield (ci-après les « Principes ») et s’engage à soumettre aux Principes toutes les données à caractère personnel en provenance de l’UE en s’appuyant sur le cadre du Privacy Shield. Les personnes auprès desquelles Subsplash recueille des données à caractère personnel dans le cadre du Privacy Shield ont le droit d’accéder à leurs données à caractère personnel en contactant Subsplash [ici](https://www.subsplash.com/legal/data-request) ou à l’adresse [\[email protected\]](https://www.subsplash.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). En tant qu’entreprise certifiée du Privacy Shield, Subsplash est assujettie aux pouvoirs d’enquête et d’application de la loi de la Federal Trade Commission ou de toute autre entité réglementaire autorisée aux États-Unis.

Vous pouvez accéder à la Liste du Privacy Shield [ici](https://www.privacyshield.gov/list).

**Avis et choix**

Lorsque Subsplash recueille des Informations à caractère personnel auprès de personnes physiques, elle peut partager ces informations avec des organisations clientes ou des tiers comme décrit ci-dessus dans la Politique de protection de la vie privée. Il incombe à ces personnes d’examiner la politique de protection de la vie privée de l’organisation cliente ; elles auront ensuite le choix de s’abonner ou non aux services de Subsplash. Au moment de s’abonner aux services de Subsplash, un lien vers la politique de protection de la vie privée de Subsplash leur sera fourni lorsque leur seront demandées leurs Informations à caractère personnel.

Dans le cas où Subsplash n’est pas le responsable ni le collecteur des Informations à caractère personnel, mais uniquement le prestataire de services de traitement des données, elle n’a pas les moyens de donner le choix ni les moyens de limiter l’utilisation et la divulgation des Informations à caractère personnel ou d’aviser lorsque ces personnes sont invitées à fournir des Informations à caractère personnel à Subsplash. Dans ces cas là, Subsplash suivra les instructions du responsable de ces informations, fournira les mesures techniques et organisationnelles appropriées pour protéger les données à caractère personnel contre la destruction accidentelle ou illégale ou la perte accidentelle, l’altération, la divulgation ou l’accès non autorisé et, dans la mesure où cela est approprié, aider le responsable à répondre aux personnes exerçant leurs droits en vertu des Principes.

Dans le contexte d’une transmission ultérieure, Subsplash est chargée de traiter les Informations à caractère personnel qu’elle reçoit en vertu du Privacy Shield et de les transférer ultérieurement à un tiers agissant comme agent en son nom. Subsplash demeure responsable en vertu des Principes si son agent traite ces Informations à caractère personnel de façon incompatible avec les Principes, sauf si l’organisation prouve qu’elle n’est pas responsable de l’événement donnant lieu au préjudice.

**Divulgation à des tiers**

Subsplash ne saurait divulguer des Informations à caractère personnel à des tiers sans informer les personnes concernées qu’une telle divulgation peut avoir lieu. Dans les cas où Subsplash recueille des informations à caractère personnel auprès de personnes concernées avant de divulguer les Informations à caractère personnel à un tiers, Subsplash est tenu d’informer la personne concernée du fait que ses Informations à caractère personnel peuvent être divulguées. Si ces personnes ne souhaitent pas que leurs Informations à caractère personnel soient divulguées à un quelconque tiers, il leur convient de ne pas s’inscrire aux services de Subsplash. En ce qui concerne Subsplash Giving, les informations du donateur sont partagées avec le bénéficiaire du don. Le bénéficiaire du don peut utiliser un tiers pour la réception et la gestion de ces informations et il incombe aux donateurs d’examiner les politiques de protection de la vie privée du bénéficiaire de don à cet égard.

Dans le cas de tiers (par exemple les églises) pour qui Subsplash recueille des Informations à caractère personnel, Subsplash doit conclure un contrat qui stipule que ces données ne peuvent être traitées qu’à des fins limitées et précisées qui soient conformes avec le consentement fourni et que ces tiers fourniront le même niveau de protection qu’exigent les Principes. Pour les agents bénéficiaires tiers (par exemple les prestataires de services de traitement des paiements) d’Informations à caractère personnel, Subsplash est tenu de ne transférer ces données qu’à des fins limitées et précisées, vérifier que l’agent a l’obligation de fournir au moins le même niveau de protection de la vie privée qu’exigent les Principes; et, à la réception d’un avis, de prendre des mesures raisonnables et appropriées pour arrêter un traitement non autorisé et y remédier.

**Sécurité des données**

Subsplash est tenu de prendre des mesures raisonnables pour protéger les Informations à caractère personnel contre tout usage abusif, perte, accès non autorisé, divulgation, altération et destruction. Subsplash a mis en place des procédures physiques, électroniques et de gestion appropriées pour protéger et sécuriser les informations contre la perte, l’abus et l’accès non autorisé, ou la divulgation, l’altération ou la destruction. Subsplash ne peut pas garantir la sécurité des informations qui se trouvent sur Internet ou qui sont transmises par ce moyen.

**Intégrité des données**

Subsplash ne saurait traiter les Informations à caractère personnel que d’une manière qui est pertinente et compatible aux fins pour lesquelles elles ont été recueillies ou autorisées par les personnes qui ont fourni les informations. Dans la mesure nécessaire à ces fins, Subsplash est tenue de prendre toutes les mesures raisonnables pour s’assurer que les Informations à caractère personnel sont exactes, complètes, actuelles et fiables pour l’usage prévu.

**Accès**

Dans les cas où Subsplash recueille des Informations à caractère personnel directement des personnes concernées, Subsplash permet à celles-ci d’accéder à leurs Informations à caractère personnel et leur permet de corriger, de modifier ou de supprimer des informations inexactes, sauf dans les cas où la charge ou le coût de la fourniture de l’accès serait disproportionné par rapport aux risques pour la protection de la vie privée de la personne concernée dans ledit cas ou lorsque les droits de personnes autres que la personne concernée seraient violés. Comme indiqué ci-dessus, vous ne pouvez pas supprimer toutes les informations si vous souhaitez maintenir un compte avec Subsplash et Subsplash a l’obligation de conserver certaines informations concernant les transactions de Subsplash Giving et des utilisateurs applicables.

**Recours, mise en application et responsabilité**

**a)** Règlement des litiges

Si vous avez déposé une plainte auprès de Subsplash et qu’elle n’a pas été traitée adéquatement, Subsplash  désigne JAMS comme organe indépendant de règlement de différends pour traiter les plaintes concernant la collecte d’Informations à caractère personnel de Subsplash et fournir les recours appropriés. Cet organe ne facture pas ses services à la partie plaignante. Suivez ce [lien](https://www.jamsadr.com/file-an-eu-us-privacy-shield-or-safe-harbor-claim) vers le formulaire de soumission de plainte pour l’organe de règlement de différends mentionné ci-dessus.

**b)** Arbitrage exécutoire

Si vos réclamations concernant les données couvertes par le Privacy Shield UE–États-Unis n’ont pas été résolues par le règlement de différend directement avec Subsplash ou par le biais du règlement de différend indépendant décrit ci-dessus, ces « réclamations résiduelles » peuvent être entendues par un « Panel du Privacy Shield » composé d’un ou de trois arbitres comme convenu entre les parties. Le Panel du Privacy Shield peut uniquement accorder un redressement équitable, non pécuniaire et spécifique selon la personne (par exemple accès aux données, correction, suppression des données en question de la personne) nécessaire pour remédier à la violation des Principes, uniquement en ce qui concerne la personne concernée. Aucun dommage-intérêt, coût, frais et autre recours ne peuvent être octroyés et chaque partie supporte ses propres frais d’avocats. Cette option d’arbitrage n’est disponible que pour une personne physique pour décider de « réclamations résiduelles », que Subsplash ait ou non violé ses obligations en vertu des Principes à l’égard de cette personne et que ladite violation reste entièrement ou partiellement non réglée.

**c)** RGPD (Règlement Général Sur La Protection Des Données)

Le GDPR remplace la Directive 95/46/EC et est en vigueur depuis le 25 mai 2018. La déclaration suivante est prévue comme complément à la discussion qui précède sur le Privacy Shield UE–États-Unis. En ce qui concerne les données à caractère personnel recueillies et contrôlées par Subsplash, sous réserve des limitations et restrictions énoncées dans le débat qui précède, les personnes concernées de l’UE conservent leurs droits entiers d’être informées des fins de nos activités de traitement au moment de la collecte, de retirer leur consentement, de consulter, rectifier, transporter et effacer leurs données à caractère personnel, de s’opposer au traitement pour des efforts de marketing direct et de s’opposer lorsqu’elles font l’objet de décisions fondées sur le traitement automatisé. En ce qui concerne les données à caractère personnel recueillies par des tiers et pour lesquelles Subsplash n’est que le prestataire des services de traitement, les personnes concernées de l’UE doivent contacter le responsable (par exemple une église ou un ministère) en ce qui concerne leurs droits d’être informées des fins de nos activités de traitement au moment de la collecte, de retirer leur consentement, de consulter, rectifier, transporter et effacer leurs données à caractère personnel de s’opposer au traitement pour des efforts de marketing direct et de s’opposer lorsqu’elles font l’objet de décisions fondées sur le traitement automatisé. Ces droits peuvent être assujettis à certaines restrictions et limitations comme indiqué dans le débat sur le Privacy Shield UE–États-Unis. 

Nos agents de traitement des données qui aideront gratuitement les résidents de l’UE avec ces demandes peuvent être joints à l’adresse [\[email protected\]](https://www.subsplash.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

Subsplash comprend que l’adoption de pratiques de sécurité pour les données au niveau mondial n’est pas une activité ponctuelle. L’approche de protection de la vie privée dès la conception (« privacy bt design ») de Subsplash exige que nos niveaux par défaut de protection des données de l’utilisateur soient automatiquement réglés au niveau le plus élevé. Dans le cas peu probable d’une violation des données, Subsplash en avise les personnes concernées et les autorités de contrôle de l’UE selon les procédures indiquées aux Articles 33 et 34 du GDPR.

Nous ne recueillons pas intentionnellement les données à caractère personnel d’enfants et nous ne personnalisons aucun de nos services à leur intention.

VeraSafe a été désigné comme représentant de Subsplash dans l’Union européenne pour les questions de protection des données, conformément à l’Article 27 du Règlement général sur la protection des données de l’Union européenne. Il est possible de contacter VeraSafe, en plus du responsable de la protection de la vie privée, uniquement pour les questions concernant le traitement des données à caractère personnel. Pour poser une question, veuillez contacter VeraSafe à l’aide de ce [formulaire de contact](https://verasafe.com/fr/public-resources/contact-data-protection-representative/) ou par téléphone au: +420 228 881 031.

Il est également possible de contacter VeraSafe à l’adresse suivante:

VeraSafe Ireland Ltd.

Unit 3D North Point House

North Point Business Park

New Mallow Road

Cork T23AT2P

Irlande

### CONFIDENTIALITÉ DES DONNÉES POUR LES RÉSIDENTS DE CALIFORNIE

Cette section s'applique uniquement aux visiteurs et utilisateurs de notre site et de nos services qui résident dans l’État de Californie. Nous avons adopté cet avis pour nous conformer à la loi California Consumer Privacy Act de 2018 (ci-après la « CCPA ») et à la loi California Online Privacy Protection Act (ci-après la « CalOPPA »), et tout terme défini dans la CCPA ou la CalOPPA a la même signification lorsqu’il est utilisé dans le présent avis.

Aux fins de la présente section, « personne concernée de Californie » signifie : 1) une personne qui se trouve dans l’État de Californie dans un but autre que temporaire ou transitoire et 2) une personne qui est domicilié dans l’État de Californie qui se trouve hors de l’État de Californie dans un but temporaire ou transitoire.

**Informations Que Nous Recueillons**

Subsplash recueille des informations qui identifient, concernent, décrivent, font référence, peuvent être associées ou peuvent être raisonnablement liées, directement ou indirectement, à une personne concernée de Californie particulière ou à un appareil particulier (ci-après « Informations à caractère personnel »). Subsplash a en particulier recueilli les catégories suivantes d’Informations à caractère personnel de personnes concernées de Californie au cours des douze (12) derniers mois:

### ‍

Catégorie

**Exemples**

Recueillons-nous ces données?

Identifiants

Vrai nom, surnom, adresse postale, identifiant personnel unique, identifiant en ligne, adresse de protocole Internet (IP), adresse électronique, nom de compte, numéro de sécurité sociale, numéro de permis de conduire, numéro de passeport ou autres identifiants similaires

Oui

Caractéristiques de classifications protégées aux termes des lois californiennes ou fédérales

Race, sexe, ethnicité, handicap

Non

Informations commerciales

Archives de biens personnels, de produits ou services achetés, obtenus ou envisagés, ou autres historiques d’achat ou de consommation ou tendances

Non

Informations biométriques

Empreintes digitales, traits faciaux, voix, cadence de saisie

Oui

Informations sur les activités sur Internet ou autres réseaux électroniques

Les informations concernant l’utilisation d’un site, d’un logiciel ou d’une application

Oui

Données de géolocalisation

Emplacement physique

Oui

Informations audio, électroniques, visuelles, thermiques, olfactives ou autres similaires

Enregistrements d’une personne concernée de Californie

Oui

Informations professionnelles ou liées à l’emploi

Lieu de travail, emploi actuel, durée de l’emploi, position ou titre

Oui

Informations sur l’éducation

Des informations qui ne sont pas des informations personnellement identifiables non accessibles au public telles que définies dans la loi Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA)

Non

Déductions tirées de l’une quelconque des informations identifiées ci-dessus

Les informations utilisées pour créer un profil de la personne concernée de Californie reflétant ses préférences, ses caractéristiques, ses tendances psychologiques, ses prédispositions, son comportement, son attitude, son intelligence, ses capacités et ses aptitudes

Oui

Sources d’Informations à caractère personnel. Subsplash obtient les Informations à caractère personnel énumérées ci-dessus des sources suivantes:

Source

Exemple

Recevons-nous de cette source?

Directement de vous

À partir de formulaires que vous remplissez ou de commandes pour des produits et services que vous achetez.

Oui

Indirectement de vous

En observant vos actions sur le service.

Oui

Tiers

Nous recevons des information provenant de nos prestataires tiers, tels que:

* Les partenaires d’authentification (qui peuvent nous fournir des Informations à caractère personnel concernant les utilisateurs qui s’authentifient avec nos services par le biais d’un tiers)
* Les prestataires de services technologiques (qui peuvent nous fournir des Informations à caractère personnel sous forme d’information sur l’utilisation, d’adresses IP, etc. des utilisateurs de notre site et de nos services)
* Les partenaires de paiement (qui peuvent nous fournir des Informations à caractère personnel afin de traiter les paiements des utilisateurs)
* Les partenaires publicitaires (qui peuvent nous fournir des informations au sujet des utilisateurs qui voient nos publicités)

Oui

**Utilisation Des Informations À Caractère Personnel**

Nous pouvons utiliser ou divulguer les Informations à caractère personnel que nous recueillons pour une ou plusieurs des fins professionnelles suivantes:

A.Pour réaliser l’objectif pour lequel vous avez fourni l’information. Par exemple, si vous partagez votre nom et vos coordonnées pour demander un devis ou poser une question au sujet de nos produits ou de nos services, nous utiliserons ces Informations à caractère personnel pour répondre à votre demande. Si vous créez un compte sur nos services, les Informations à caractère personnel que vous fournissez dans le cadre du processus de création du compte peuvent être vues par d’autres titulaires de compte et nous pouvons utiliser ces informations pour vérifier votre identité lorsque vous accédez à votre compte. Nous pouvons utiliser les Informations à caractère personnel que vous nous donnez pour vous fournir un soutien technique. En outre, nous pouvons utiliser les informations ci-dessus:

a. Pour fournir, soutenir, personnaliser et développer nos sites Web, produits et/ou services

b. Pour créer, maintenir, adapter et sécuriser votre compte chez nous

c. Pour traiter vos demandes, achats, transactions et paiements ainsi que pour prévenir la fraude transactionnelle

d. Pour vous fournir du soutien et pour répondre à vos demandes, y compris pour enquêter et traiter vos préoccupations, ainsi que pour suivre et améliorer nos réponses

e. Pour aider à maintenir la sécurité, la sûreté et l’intégrité de notre site Web, de nos produits et services, de nos bases de données et autres actifs technologiques, et de nos activités commerciales

f.  Pour répondre aux demandes d’application de la loi et selon les exigences des lois applicables, des décisions judiciaires ou des règlements gouvernementaux

g. Tel que décrit au moment où nous recueillons vos Informations à caractère personnel ou selon ce qui est prévu autrement dans la CCPA.

Subsplash ne recueille pas de catégories supplémentaires d’Informations à caractère personnel et n’utilise pas les Informations à caractère personnel recueillies à des fins substantiellement différentes, sans lien ou incompatibles, sans vous avoir avisé au préalable.  

Subsplash ne vend pas vos Informations à caractère personnel. Subsplash partage les Informations à caractère personnel avec ses prestataires de services tiers et autres sous-traitants afin de vous fournir le service.

**Vos Droits Et Choix**

La présente section décrit vos droits aux termes de la CCPA et explique comment les exercer.

Vous avez le droit de demander que nous vous divulguions certaines informations relatives à notre collecte et notre utilisation de vos Informations à caractère personnel au cours de 12 derniers mois. Une fois votre demande reçue et vérifiée, nous vous divulguerons:

A. Les catégories d’Informations à caractère personnel recueillies par nous à votre sujet

B. Les catégories de sources d’Informations à caractère personnel recueillies par nous à votre sujet

C. Notre objectif professionnel ou commercial pour la collecte ou la vente de ces Informations à caractère personnel

D. Les catégories de tiers avec qui nous partageons ces Informations à caractère personnel

E. Les éléments précis d’Informations à caractère personnel recueillies par nous à votre sujet (aussi appelé demande de portabilité des données)

F. Si nous avons vendu ou divulgué vos Informations à caractère personnel à une fin professionnelle, deux listes distinctes divulguant:

a. les ventes, identifiant les catégories d’Informations à caractère personnel que chaque catégorie de bénéficiaire a achetées

b. les divulgations à une fin professionnelle, identifiant les catégories d’Informations à caractère personnel que chaque catégorie de bénéficiaire a obtenues

Vous avez le droit de demander que nous supprimions toute information personnelle recueillie auprès de vous et conservée, sous réserve de certaines exceptions. Une fois votre demande reçue et vérifiée, nous supprimerons (et demanderons à nos prestataires de services de supprimer) vos Informations à caractère personnel de nos archives, à moins qu’une exception ne s’applique.

Nous pouvons refuser votre demande de suppression si la conservation de l’information est nécessaire pour que nous ou nos prestataires de service puissions:

A. Achever la transaction pour laquelle nous avons recueilli vos Informations à caractère personnel, fournir un bien ou un service que vous avez demandé, prendre des mesures raisonnablement prévues dans le contexte de notre relation commerciale continue avec vous, ou exécuter notre contrat avec vous

B. Détecter les incidents de sécurité, nous protéger contre les activités malveillantes, trompeuses, frauduleuses ou illégales, ou poursuivre les personnes responsables de telles activités

C. Déboguer les produits afin d’identifier et de réparer les erreurs qui nuisent à la fonctionnalité existante prévue

D. Exercer la liberté d’expression, garantir le droit d’une autre personne concernée de Californie à exercer ses droits de liberté d’expression ou un autre droit prévu par la loi

E. Nous conformer à la loi California Electronic Communications Privacy Act (Code pénal de Californie § 1546 et suivants)

F. Participer à des recherches scientifiques, historiques ou statistiques publiques ou évaluées par des pairs dans l’intérêt général, qui respectent toutes les autres lois applicables en matière d’éthique et de protection de la vie privée lorsque la suppression des informations risque de rendre impossible ou de compromettre gravement la réalisation de la recherche, si vous avez donné votre consentement éclairé au préalable

G. Permettre uniquement des utilisations internes qui sont raisonnablement alignées sur les attentes de la personne concernée de Californie en fonction de votre relation avec nous

H. Nous conformer à une obligation légale et

I. Faire d’autres utilisations internes et légales de ces informations qui sont compatibles avec le contexte dans lequel vous les avez fournies.

Pour exercer vos droits d’accès, de portabilité des données et de suppression décrits ci-dessus, veuillez soumettre une demande vérifiable de personne concernée de Californie en nous soumettant votre demande [ici](https://www.subsplash.com/legal/data-request), en nous envoyant un courrier électronique à l’adresse [\[email protected\]](https://www.subsplash.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection), ou en téléphonant au (206) 965-8090.

Vous seul ou une personne inscrite auprès du secrétaire d’État de Californie, que vous autorisez à agir en votre nom, pouvez faire une demande vérifiable de personne concernée de Californie concernant vos Informations à caractère personnel. Vous pouvez également faire une demande vérifiable de personne concernée de Californie au nom de votre enfant mineur.

Vous ne pouvez faire une demande vérifiable de personne concernée de Californie que deux fois par période de douze (12) mois. La demande vérifiable de personne concernée de Californie doit:

A. Fournir suffisamment d’informations pour nous permettre de vérifier raisonnablement que vous êtes la personne dont nous avons recueilli les Informations à caractère personnel ou un représentant autorisé et

B. Décrire votre demande de façon suffisamment détaillée pour nous permettre de la comprendre, de l’évaluer et d’y répondre adéquatement.

Nous ne pouvons répondre à votre demande ni vous fournir des Informations à caractère personnel si nous ne pouvons pas vérifier votre identité ou votre pouvoir de faire une demande et confirmer que les Informations à caractère personnel vous concernent. Il n’est pas obligatoire de créer un compte chez nous pour faire une demande vérifiable de personne concernée de Californie. Nous n’utiliserons que les Informations à caractère personnel fournies dans une demande vérifiable de personne concernée de Californie pour vérifier l’identité du demandeur ou son pouvoir à faire la demande.

Nous aspirons à répondre à une demande vérifiable de personne concernée de Californie dans les quarante-cinq (45) jours suivant réception de la demande. S’il nous faut plus de temps (jusqu’à quatre-vingt-dix (90) jours), nous vous informons de la ou des raisons pour lesquelles une prolongation est nécessaire et sa durée prévue. Toute divulgation que nous faisons ne couvre que la période de douze (12) mois précédant la réception de votre demande. Le cas échéant, nous fournissons dans notre réponse les raisons pour lesquelles nous ne pouvons nous conformer à votre demande. Pour les demandes de portabilité des données, nous choisissons un format qui soit facilement utilisable pour vos Informations à caractère personnel et qui puisse vous permettre de transmettre les informations d’une entité à une autre sans entrave. 

Nous ne facturons pas de frais pour traiter votre demande vérifiable de personne concernée de Californie ou pour y répondre, à moins qu’elle soit excessive, répétitive ou manifestement infondée. Si nous déterminons que la demande justifie des frais, nous vous indiquons pourquoi nous avons pris cette décision et nous vous fournissons une estimation des coûts avant d’exécuter votre demande. Nous nous réservons le droit de refuser de répondre aux demandes vérifiables de personnes concernées de Californie qui sont excessives, répétitives ou manifestement infondées.

**Droit à la discrimination**

Nous ne ferons pas de discrimination à votre encontre pour avoir exercé l’un de vos droits au titre de la CCPA. Nous ne prendrons aucune des mesures suivantes à votre encontre en réponse à un exercice de vos droits:

A. Vous refuser des biens ou des services.

B. Vous facturer des prix ou des tarifs différents pour des biens ou des services, y compris en octroyant des rabais ou autres avantages, ou en imposant des pénalités.

C. Vous fournir un niveau ou une qualité de biens ou de services différents.

D. Suggérer que vous pourriez recevoir un prix ou un tarif différent pour des biens ou des services ou un niveau ou une qualité de biens ou de services différents.

**Divulgations** **concernant l’interdiction desuivi de Californie**

Subsplash ne suit pas ses clients au fil du temps ni sur les sites Web de tiers afin d’offrir des publicités ciblées et, par conséquent, ne répond pas aux signaux d’interdiction de suivi (DNT – Do Not Track).  Tout tiers dont le contenu est intégré aux sites Web, aux logiciels ou aux applications mobiles de Subsplash (par exemple les fonctions sociales) peuvent installer des cookies sur le navigateur d’un utilisateur et/ou obtenir des informations sur le fait qu’un navigateur Web a visité un site Web Subsplash spécifique à partir d’une certaine adresse IP. Les tiers ne peuvent recueillir aucune autre information personnelle identifiable sur les sites Web de Subsplash à moins que vous les leur fournissiez directement.

### INFORMATIONS SPÉCIALES POUR LES RÉSIDENTS DU NEVADA

Les résidents de l’État du Nevada ont le droit de ne pas accepter la vente de certains éléments de leurs informations à d’autres sociétés qui vendront ou cèderont sous licence leurs informations à d’autres personnes. Subsplash ne vend ni ne loue pas vos coordonnées à d’autres spécialistes du marketing ou à toute autre tiers. Si vous êtes un résident du Nevada et que vous avez d’autres questions, veuillez nous contacter [ici](https://www.subsplash.com/legal/data-request) ou par courrier électronique à l’adresse [\[email protected\]](https://www.subsplash.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). 

### CAMPAGNES SPÉCIALISÉES PARTENAIRES

De temps à autre, Subsplash peut collaborer avec des organisations partenaires pour développer et distribuer du contenu spécialisé. Les utilisateurs qui participent aux campagnes de marketing spécialisées en remplissant notre formulaire d’inscription et en téléchargeant le contenu applicable sont concernés par [l'Avis supplémentaire de protection de la vie privée](https://www.subsplash.com/legal/supplemental-privacy-notice) en sus de la présente Politique de protection de la vie privée.

### L’ENGAGEMENT DE L’ENTREPRISE TOUTE ENTIÈRE ENVERS LA PROTECTION DE VOTRE VIE PRIVÉE

Pour nous assurer que vos Informations à caractère personnel sont en sécurité, nous communiquons ces directives en matière de protection de la vie privée aux salariés de Subsplash et nous appliquons strictement les garanties en matière de protection de la vie privée au sein de l’entreprise.

### LIBERTÉ DES DEMANDES D’INFORMATION

Si vous communiquez ou faites un don à une organisation ou institution qui est assujettie à une loi fédérale ou du secteur public provincial ou d’État concernant la « liberté d’information » ou l’« accès à l’information », veuillez noter que les informations concernant votre communication et/ou votre don peuvent être divulguées à des tiers conformément aux procédures disponibles en vertu de ces lois.

### DEMANDES, RÉCLAMATIONS ET RÈGLEMENT DE DIFFÉRENDS

Si vous souhaitez vérifier, corriger ou supprimer toute information personnelle que nous avons recueillie, ou si vous avez des questions ou des préoccupations, ou si vous avez des réclamations, veuillez nous contacter [ici](https://www.subsplash.com/legal/data-request) ou par courrier électronique à l’adresse [\[email protected\]](https://www.subsplash.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). S’il y a un différend entre vous et Subsplash concernant vos Informations à caractère personnel ou la présente politique, vous acceptez de déployer des efforts raisonnables pour résoudre ce différend avec Subsplash de façon informelle, et de consulter et négocier avec Subsplash en toute bonne foi pour parvenir à une solution juste et équitable.  

### QUESTIONS SUR LA PROTECTION DE LA VIE PRIVÉE

Si vous avez des questions ou des préoccupations concernant la politique de protection de la vie privée de Subsplash, veuillez contacter notre responsable de la protection de la vie privée. Ce responsable peut être contacté à l’adresse suivante:

Subsplash, Inc. 750 N Saint Paul St Ste 250, PMB 41141, Dallas, Texas 75201-3206 or [\[email protected\]](https://www.subsplash.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

‍

Connect

[Support](https://www.subsplash.com/support)[System status](https://status.subsplash.com/)[\[email protected\]](https://www.subsplash.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)[Talk to sales: 469-564-3922](tel:+14695643922)

PLATFORM

ABOUT US

LEGAL

Cookies settings
